在并购方面
In terms of Miand A action
据说 GoJo和韦斯达酝酿已久的交易
we're hearing that GoJo and Waystar
最快可能在明天就拍板定案
Could seal their long-gestated deal as soon as tomorrow.
盛传的法规方面的顾虑 已经消除
Word is that regulatory concerns have receded
所以 卢卡斯·马特森可能 很快
So Lukas Matsson may soon take control
就会控制 已故的 洛根·罗伊的帝国
of the deceased Logan Roy's empire
将其纳入他的流媒体 博弈 体育 与社群应用软件
to add to his streaming, betting, sports, and socials, everything app
好
All right.
好 好
Okay, okay
各位 要把握当下
Carpe the diem, people
阿泰 咱们过一遍董事会的报告吧
Telly, let's run this board presentation, shall we?
对 好极了 谢了
Yeah. Great. Thanks.
太好了
Good stuff.
那个...  -怎么样
So...  -What?
刚刚是斯图伊的人
Just Stewy. That was his guy
然后...  -所以呢
And...  -Yep
我觉得 他跑票了
Yeah, I don't think we got him
好...
Cool, cool.
真的吗
Really?
他在哪里 直接帮我打给他
Where is he? Get me him direct.
这可能只是烟雾弹 我想
It might be smokescreen. I think..
对 可能是烟雾弹
Yeah, that'll be... that'll be smokescreen
我可以争取到斯图伊
I can pull in Stew.
肯 我...  -天啊
Ken, I...  -Man.
我觉得股东不支持我们
I don't think we have the shareholders
董事会的票数也不足以阻止这件事
and I don't think we have the board numbers to stop this
我会争取到足够票数
I'll get the votes.
如果时间比较充裕的话...
If we had more time...
肯 我们明天...  -我会争取到足够票数
but by tomorrow, Ken, we...  -I'll get the votes.
你能说一下大概的情况吗
You want to just... outline the path here.
好 我 尤恩 保罗 和戴维
Okay. I got fuckin' me, I got Ewan, I got Paul, I got Dewi
都是铁票 所以 好吗
Locked. So, yeah?
很好 还有呢
Okay, great. And?
我还是有把握可以争取到斯图伊
And I still think I can get Stewy
可能有桑妮亚 跟弗兰克
I think maybe Sonya. Maybe Frank
能采取的路线很多
There are multiple... multiple routes
目前你有四票 其中一票是…
Right now, you have four and one of them..
罗曼会来吗
And is Roman even gonna show?
他会投票吗  -别担心罗曼
Is he gonna vote?   -Don't worry about Roman.
他的立场是什么  -我不知道
But just where does he stand?   -I don't know.
我不知道 我不知道 我什么都不知道
I don't know, I don't know. I don't fuckin' know.
好吗
Okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吗 这样会让你好过点吗
Okay? Does that make you feel better?
我不知道罗曼在哪里 也不知道他的立场
I don't know where he is, I don't know where he stands
但 他那票 包在我身上 好吗
But I got him. Okay?
没问题的 泰利熊
I fucking got this, Telly bear
继   承   之   战
第 4 季  第 10 集
【大 结 局】
好的
Okay.
我想 他们失去斯图伊了 他动摇了
I think they lost Stewy. He's wonked.
肯德尔现在已经被我们关进后备箱
So, that means we got Kendall in the trunk
五花大绑 任我们摆布了
all trussed up and ready to fuckin' bake.
怎么样  -太好了
Yeah?   -It's good.
好的 因为我们这方有我在 这是当然的
Okay. 'Cause, you know, we got me, obviously, here.
我 西蒙 弗兰克 桑蒂 和桑迪 也都稳了
Me, Simon, Frank, Sandi,and Sandy, locked
还有斯图伊 我…
And then Stewy, I..
听着 他很会撂狠话
Look, he talks a lot of shit,
但 我觉得 他会留下来
but I think he's... he's gonna stay
他不会跑票
He's not gonna split
因为 有钱能使鬼推磨 对吧
'Cause money, honey. Right?
再来 有黛安·刘 桑妮亚
So, then we got Diane Liu, Sonya.
这样 票数就够了
And then we... we have it.
如果挖走戴维 保罗 和尤恩
Then, if we peel off Dewi, Paul, and Ewan
那 反对的 就只剩下肯和罗曼
then there's only, like, Ken and Rome in the against.
那根本... 而且 罗曼有可能会不来参加
That's fuckin'... And Rome might not even show up
他会在某个性爱地牢 被人打屁屁消愁
from whatever jerk dungeon he's being pity-spanked in.
满意吗
You happy?
非常满意...对
Very happy. Very... yeah
对 很好
Yeah. Good.
成功了 是的
Success. Yeah.
我等等要找弗兰克
Oh, and I'm checking in on Frank
如果你还想用传统的签约法
if you still wanna do the old-school signing
好极了  -你知道的 我以新任CEO的身份 对吧
Perfect.  -You know, me as new CEO? Yes?
你的名单呢 上头有谁
And your list? What's... what's on..
想谈汤姆的事吗
You wanna talk Tom?
我知道 你思考过泛美网科的事
Or, I don't know, you've been thinking about ATN
你可以说出来 我不介意
and just... just say out loud, it's no big deal for me
我们开过几次初步会议
Well, we've... we've had some initial, like, vibe meets.
对 他已经屁滚尿流了
Yeah, I mean, he's shitting himself.
对 普男跟十倍男之间的差异
Yeah, well, the... the delta between a guy and a 10x guy
显然是生死之别
is obviously life and death
泛美网科很重要 所以...  -当然
and ATN is central, so...  -Sure.
汤姆 汤姆 是的
Tom, Tom. Yeah.
我不确定 你觉得呢
I don't know. What... what do you think?
他很有能力
Okay, well, he's very competent
但 假如你觉得他烦 或是太复杂了
but if he irks you or it's complicated
没关系的 好吗
it is okay, yeah?
他很适合待在大企业
He is very plausible corporate matter
但也随时可以被取代
but he's also just a highly interchangeable modular part
这话我可以当面讲给他听  -好的
And I would say that to his face.  -Okay
但 如果我们要的是连贯性
Okay, but if we wanted continuity
因为最近的变化太多
because there's been a lot of changes
泛美网科的发展如火如荼 他的人缘很好
you know, ATN is going gangbusters and he is well-liked
如果他要留下来 我也没意见
So, if he were to stay on, that would also be okay with me.
好 谢谢你告诉我  -好
Okay. Good to know.  -Yeah.
先不提私人感情
This is separate, feelings aside
汤姆肯定会去拍 最厉害的人的马屁
Tom will honestly suck the biggest dick in the room
这只是我的评估
That's just my assessment.
爱弥漫在空中  -是啊
Love is in the air.  -Yeah
抱歉 不好意思
Sorry. Excuse me.
我马上好
Yeah. Just one sec.
喂 亲爱的 情况如何
Hello, darling. Is this... How are things going?
是 好 很好 很好 谢了  -太好了
Yep, fine. Good. Good, thanks.  -Great.
我只想知道 你有没有可能来
I just wanted to know if there was any chance of you coming
我很想去
Yeah, I mean, look, I would love to.
但是 你知道的 排不出时间
but I think, you know, fuckin' schedules
还有...董事会
and... and board.
对 我知道 但是…
Yeah, I know, but..
这里有个 我觉得 你会想见的人
well, there's somebody here I think you might want to see.
我答应过不会讲 但...
I promised I wouldn't say, but..
他是你两个哥哥之一
it's one of your brothers.
而且 不是肯德尔
And it's not Kendall
好 我来破解一下你的密码
Okay. Well, let me crack the code.
我只觉得 你会想知道
I just thought you'd like to know.
好...
Yeah, well..
我想一下 但是…
let me have a think, but let's..
咱们...想个办法进行
Yeah, let's try and... try and make this work
好吗  -好极了
Shall we?   -Great.
那个专访还可以吗
That okay? That profile bullshit?
你是说这个漫画吗  -对
The cartoon?   -Yeah.
我觉得很好笑  -对
I think it's funny.  -Yeah.
像是...“看我 看我啊”
Like, "Oh, look at me, look at me.'
你知道吗 很好  -对 因为我…
You know? It's good.  -Yeah. 'Cause I..
我可以找记者 你知道的
Cause I can get the journalist, you know
也许可以处理网络上的…
maybe take the online...
不用 我不在乎
No, no. I don't give a fuck
反正 一直都有人想冲着我来
People always try to fuckin'... get at me, you know?
好吧  -但是都不成功
Okay.  -They can't.
刚刚是我同事打来的
Look, that was... that was an associate of mine
说找到罗曼了
indicating they got a fix on Roman
我去把罗曼也搞定 如何
So, why don't I just fuckin' go and nail Roman as well?
能让董事会全数通过的感觉 一定很棒
It would be so nice just to get unanimity across the board, you know?
我们大家 微笑地出现在大众面前
All of us smiling in public, just.
干净利落地展开我们的王朝
just nice clean start for the start of our reign
好  -好吗 因为...
All right.  -Yeah, 'cause..
从企业观点来看 如果我们在不同阵营
You know, corporate narrative, if we're on separate sides
看起来会像麦克白夫人的续集
it looks like Lady Macbeth Part Two
那实在不…
and that's not...
总之
It would be... it would, just in an...
感觉会很好 小心谨慎地
It would be nice, in an abundance of caution
迎来完美的结局
just to... close nice.
对 对  -好极了
Yeah, yeah.  -Great.
好的 随时打电话给我
All right, call me whenever, wherever.
好  -我都有空
Yep.  -I'm available.
好吗 咱们搞定这件事吧
Okay? Yeah? Let's fuckin' do this.
去解决他  -好吗
Go get 'em.  -Yeah?
小西 听到什么消息了吗
Hey, Shiv. What are you hearing?
罗曼在我妈妈家
Rome's at my mom's
我正要去搞定他
So, I'm on my way to bag him.
我想让董事会全数通过
I'm looking for unanimity
好 他在你妈妈家?
Okay. He's at your mom's?
你跟卢卡斯谈过了吗
And have you spoken to Lukas?
我会被砍掉吗
Am... am I for the chop?
谈过了 我正在努力
Yeah, I mean, I'm trying.
好的 我只是有种不祥的预感
Okay. I'm just... I've got a bad feeling.
我担心第三波会裁到我
We've booked me in for the third "hang.
真的很折磨人 我…
It's excruciating. I'm just..
我担心他会想玩在线游戏
I'm scared he's gonna wanna play online games
我会有几个小时急得撞墙
and I'll be running into a wall for hours, you know?
汤姆 嘿 汤姆 我们可以认真谈谈吗
Tom. Hey, Tom. Can we have a real conversation?
马特森那里...我会尽力的
Okay, so, on the Matsson stuff...I'll do what I can. I'm trying.
至于我们的关系 我有几件事要先讲清楚
But with us, I just... I wanted to get a few things straight
对 我只希望能和和气气的
Yeah. I, just... I... Yeah. I just want it to be really nice
我们应该比照捷克斯洛伐克
And we should, we should Czechoslovakia it
就和和气气地分开
You know, we should make it all lovely, velvet, parting of the ways
所以 你没有什么要说的了?
So, for you, there's not anything left?
什么意思
Well, how do you mean?
我只是想知道
Well, I wondered if..
你懂的 我想 也许该提一下
you know, I guess I thought it might be worth raising
我们一起经历的那场疆梦
Are there any positives
有没有什么正面的地方
about the nightmare we've shared?
比方说…
As in...
我是想 如果有的话...
I guess if... if there was anything there.
如果有的话 就太方便了
if there was, then it would be so convenient.
确实很方便
Yeah, well, it would be incredibly convenient
因为那样 你就不会跟丈夫分开了
because you would be married to your husband
对 完全正确
Yeah. Exactly
而且想想 行程超好排
And then, I mean, think of the scheduling. It's mess-free.
对 你终于坠入爱河了
Yeah. You've fallen in love, finally
爱上我们排行程的机会
You've fallen in love with our scheduling opportunities.
我也 你知道 我也很希望 不要…
And I would also, you know, I would love to not to have..
西沃恩 你不喜欢考试不及格吧?
You don't like to fail a test, do you, Siobhan?
这个嘛…
Well...
听我说...我知道 我们都曾出口伤人
Look...I know that we've said the worst things.
但是 我…
But I...
我想我一直都 很怕谈感情
I think I've always just been scared in relationships of.
你知道的 就是藏在下方的东西
you know, like... the underneaths.
人最不堪的想法是什么
You know, what's the worst thing a person thinks?
但是我们知道
But we know.
但是一旦你说了和做了最不堪的事
But once you've said and done the worst things
你就自由了
you're kind of free
我想问的是…
Yeah, I guess my question is..
你对一段真正的感情有兴趣吗
are you interested in a real relationship?
老实说 我不知道
Honest to God, I don't know.
小西 我只是...我...
Shiv, I just... I..
我真的不知道
I just don't know.
好 没问题 再见
Okay. Sure. All right. Bye.
斯图伊 斯图伊 老兄
Stewy. Stewy, bro.
不要躲我
Don't hide from me.
我从这上面就看到你了
I can see you from up here.
跟我来吧 斯图伊 我们可以打赢这一仗的 好吗
Come with me, Stew. We can win this. Okay?
肯  -什么事
Ken?   -Yeah?
罗曼
Roman.
是格雷格和天杀的山姆透露的  -好的
From Greg and Rat fucker Sam.  -Okay.
好的 这下有戏唱了  -对
Okay. Now we're talking.  -Yeah.
喂 亲爱的
Hello, darling.
嘿 妈 我听说 罗曼可能在你家
Hey, Mom. So, I hear Romey might be there.
听着 很抱歉不能去参加你的聚会
Listen, I'm sorry I couldn't make your get-together
但 我有急事跟罗曼谈
but I need to speak to Roman very urgently
我不是想指责他 这是生死攸关的大事
No recriminations, but it's life or death.
他在吗
Is he there?
我不能说
I... I can't say.
你不能说?
Oh, you can't say?
他必须回来
Well, he needs to come back.
他明天打算回来吗
Is he planning to come back? For tomorrow?
那要由你们一起决定
That's for you to decide, all of you.
我...他现在很脆弱
I... he's very fragile
小西在那里吗 她是不是要过去?
And... and is Shiv there? Is she coming?
我不想谈公事 好吗
I don't want to get into a lot of business, all right?
我希望全家都能来
I want...I'd love for the whole family to be here
但 如果是要互相折磨
but if it's going to be thumbscrews
那我宁愿 不要发生在我家
I'd rather it didn't happen in my house.
好 我这就来 我这就来 我会去的 妈
Okay. I'm coming, I'm coming. I'll be there, Mom.
找到他了 找到他了  -太好了
We have him, we have him.  -All right, great.
新杰西 新杰西 我要出去一趟
New Jess, New Jess, I'm flying out.
今晚会回来 最迟明天一早
I'll be back tonight, early tomorrow latest
只带少数几个人去
Small team. Read your stuff
这些我在路上整理
I'll put this together on the move.
好吗  -好
Okay?   -Yeah, yep.
去把他抓回来 把他装箱打包
Let's get him. Let's bag him and tag him.
嘿 你好吗  -嘿 欢迎
Hey. How you doing?   -Hey. Welcome
我靠 你怎么了
Shit. What the fuck happened to you?
你好啊 真好
Hello, hello. How lovely
太好了 你带属下来了
Oh, wonderful. I see you've brought your underling with you.
对 我很忙
Yeah, well, I've got a lot going on.
究竟是怎么回事
What the fuck happened, man?
我跟你的几个朋友
Yeah, I just had a discussion with some of your pals
讨论了自由民主的好处
about the merits of liberal democracy
幸好你在这里
Okay, well, it's good that you're here, I guess
可以好好休息养伤
You can rest and recuperate
他看起来 比之前好多了
Looks a lot better than he did
他刚回来时 我都不敢看他
I couldn't look at it when he first arrived
是真的 我的眼药是彼得点的
Oh, that's true. Peter did my eyedrops
对 幸亏有他
Yeah, bless him.
我觉得眼睛很恶心
There's something about eyes, they just kind of... revolt me.
眼睛? 你是说人类都有的眼睛吗
Eyes? Like human eyes that we all have?
我老觉得眼睛是在脑袋里
I don't like to think of all these blobs of jelly
打转的 两坨果冻
rolling around in your heads
像 脸上的两颗蛋
Face eggs.
不说了 进来吧
Anyway, come on in.
这里完全没有变
Place hasn't changed
还是到处漏水
Still full of leaks.
是啊 我似乎买了天堂里唯一的鬼地方
Yeah.  -Seem to have landed myself with the only hellhole in paradise
快接电话...斯图伊
Pick up... Stewy.
斯图伊
Stewy.
斯图伊 终于啊
Stewy, there you are.
你挺我吗 快说
Are you with me? Talk to me.
好兄弟 好兄弟
Good man, good man.
我就知道 你不会那样整我
I knew you wouldn't do me dirty like that
我要先去一个地方 我找到罗曼
I'm just making a pit stop. I found Roman.
罗曼一直在我掌握之中
I mean, I always had Roman
现在只是要去确定一下
but this is just, like, nailed-nailed.
好
Okay.
跟劳伦斯·易? 沃尔特公司的劳伦斯吧
With Lawrence Yee? Vaulter Lawrence?
好
Okay.
那会怎么样
What shape does that make?
罗曼
Romey!
你在哪里
Where are you?
在吗
Hello, hello.
"猎杀红色十月“结束了
The hunt for Red fuckin' October is over.
嘿 波希雅
Hey, Portia.
好啊 这和谐的家庭
Well, well, well. Look at this fuckin' family scene.
小心点  -你还好吗
Just easy.  -Are you okay, man?
小心点  -你的脸怎么了
Easy.  -Fuck happened to your face?
你的脸怎么了  -他很脆弱 好吗 慢慢来
What happened to your face?   -He's fragile, yeah? Just easy
他很脆弱?  -去你的脆弱
He's fragile?   -Hey, fuck you, "fragile."
我才不脆弱说 什么啊
I'm not fragile. What?
别逼他 慢慢来 好吗
'Just back up, yeah? Just take it easy.
别逼他  -对
Back up?   -Yeah
干吗 我只是来他妈喝茶的
What? I'm just arriving for a cup of fucking tea.
你现在咄咄逼人  -你已经错过了下午茶
Okay, well, you're being very aggressive.  -You've missed teatime.
罗曼  -好吗 冷静点
Rome?   -Yeah? Just calm down.
你好  -我很冷静 我们可以谈谈吗
Hello.  -I'm calm. Can we talk? Okay?
天啊 我不...好吧  -我们得谈谈
Oh, God. I don't... Okay.  -We gotta talk
他们完了  -别那样跟我说话 好吗
They're fucked.  -Don't talk to me that way, okay?
对 你也完了 我们完了 大家都完了
Yeah, they're fucked, you're fucked, we're fucked, everyone's fucked
别想唬我 我不喜欢  -这是怎样?
Don't bullshit me, man. I don't like that.  -What is this?
你在说什么
What is what?
你用螺丝起子 把他撬开了吗
Did you get your little fucking screwdriver in on him?
你把他撬走了吗  -没有
You pry him open?   -No.
没有  -罗曼 那是胡说八道
No.  -Rome, that's bullshit.
我们已经脱不了身了  -是吗 对 是的
We're in this. We're in this, man.  - Yeah? Yeah. We will.
这是怎样  -她在骗你 老弟
What's going on?   -She's doing a number on you, man.
嘿 嘿 妈 嘿  -你好 亲爱的
Hey. Hey, Mom. Hey.  -Hello, darling
是 嗨  -没事吧
Yes, hi.  -Are we all right?
没事 我只是 得跟罗曼谈谈
Yeah. I just need to talk to Roman.
我在照顾罗曼
Well, I'm looking after Roman.
妈 你没有在照顾我
You're not looking after me, Mom.
好吗 我只是待在这儿  -可以保持风度吗
Okay? I'm just... I'm here.  -Well, let's be civil, please.
我正在努力保持风度 没事  -罗曼
That's what I'm doing. It's fine.  -Rome.
什么事  -你答应过我
What?   -You promised me.
你答应过我 你不会这样
Okay? You promised me you wouldn't do this.
你答应过我 不会改变心意的
You promised me your wouldn't change your mind on this
也许我食言了 抱歉 但我不在乎
Well, maybe I did, and I'm sorry and whoops, I don't give a fuck.
这是一级紧急状况 好吗
This is fuckin' Def Con One. Okay?
现在全世界就靠你了
The world is pivoting on you.
全世界就要靠一个该死的小丑了
The world is turning on a fucking clown here.
你他妈才是小丑  -看看你
Okay, you're a fucking clown, man.  -Look at you
看看你才对 你才是小丑 活在一个幻想的世界里
Look at you, man. You're a clown. Living in a fucking dream world.
你根本没什么本事…
You don't have it..
为什么要怪在我头上?
So, why are you trying to, like, fucking get into me, okay?
罗曼需要平静  -我有尤恩 我有保罗
Roman needs some peace and quiet.  -I have Ewan, I have Paul..
我有戴维 我还有斯图伊  -我被卷入一场暴力肢体冲突
I have Dewi, and I have Stewy.  -I was in a very violent fight
而且我赢了 但是我没事
which I won, by the way, but I am fine
你就...别来烦我了 好吗
I just... Just back the fuck up, okay?
大家都别再说话  -你说你要怎么投票
Everyone just stop talking.  -Okay, I'll leave you alone.
我就不烦你了 我就走
I'll go if you'll just tell me how you're voting.
你还在讲话 你还在跟我讲话
You're still talking. You're talking to me.
我不想听你说话  -拜托 像个男人
I don't want you to talk.  -Come on, man up, man.
罗曼 我需要你像男人一点  -很好 谢谢 我要走了
I need you to man up here, Roman.  -Great. Thankyou. I'm going.
别跑去躲起来  -拜托不要跟过来 不要讲话
Don't fucking hide and...  -Please don't follow me. Don't talk.
你是要留下吃饭
Are you staying to dinner
还是 大吼大叫完就走?
or are you just in and out with all the shouting?
要是场面没那么难看 我会很高兴的
'Cause I'd love it if it wasn't a horror show.
没办法 我有很重要的董事会要开
I can't, there... I have... There's a huge board meeting.
“重要的董事会“ 天啊 好了不起的大事
"Huge board meeting." Gosh, well, what an event.
我从来没有碰过这种事
That's never happened before in my life.
从来没有因为 重要的董事会 而坏了我的计划
I've never had my plans ruined by a huge board meeting before.
我很乐意留下来 我要留下来吃饭
Well, I would love to. I'm in for dinner.
太好了  -他可能很忙
Great.  -He might be busy.
你还有电话要打吧?
You gotta call some people, yeah?
他要输了 所以会很忙
You're... He's losing, so he's very busy
好 我很乐意留下来吃饭 妈 我很乐意
Yeah, that would be nice, Mom. That would be nice.
我不急着去别的地方  -太好了
I... I got nowhere to be.  -Great.
你有什么想法  -你问我有什么想法?
What do you think, man?   -What do I think?
颜色很搭
The colors go well
好迷幻 兄弟
Trippy, dude.
卢卡斯 借一步说话
Lukas. A second, please.
又让我吊在一边 吊死鬼比独裁者的生日时还多
More hang, more fucking hanging than a dictator's birthday
嘿 “颜色很搭" 语法对吗?
Hey. "The colors go well"? Is that a sentence?
对 对 颜色很搭  -说得通吗
Yeah, yeah. The colors go well.  -Does that make sense?
颜色放一起很搭  -颜色很搭
The colors go well together.  -Colors go well
对 可以  -颜色很搭
Yeah, it's okay.  -The colors go well
颜色很搭  -格雷格 你是来陪我的
The colors just go well.  -Greg, you're here for the hang
如果场面冷了
So, you know, to jump in on the little
你要来帮忙
you know, those awkward social beats
你要像是社交上的油灰腻子
you gotta be, like... like fucking social putty
你害我被吊在一边的话
Okay? You're letting me swing
他会开除我的
Okay? He's gonna fucking fire me, I know.
我需要耳目
I need ears and eyes out
了解内情的助理
You know, like, on the assistant loop
比如艾芭... 我要知道 马特森是不是打算砍掉我
Ebba... like, is he planning to kill me?
如果他赢了 如果他进来的话
If he wins, if he gets in,
你就惨了
you are fucked.
你就完蛋了
You're fucked.
好 他喜欢我 所以…
All right, well, he likes me, so..
你? 你? 二十万?
You? You? 200k?
人类史上 薪水最高的助理?
The highest-paid assistant in human history?
改朝换代了 兄弟
It's new management, bro
你的薪水会被减到 两万三万 或四万
You're gonna get busted down to 20, 30, 40k.
知道吗 是真的  -别说了
You know? Seriously.  -Stop it
如果我被开除 我想 你也完蛋了
And if I get fired, I think you are fucked
这是家族死亡大行军
It's the family death march
早起的鸟儿有罗曼?
Early bird catches the Rome?
你知道的...对
Well, you know... yeah
有几件事 你可能会有兴趣
Just... a couple of things you might be interested in
我把斯图伊给抢回来了  -是吗
I got Stewy back.  -Oh, yeah?
太好了 你也知道
Sure. Well, you know..
就算他说的是实话
even if he's telling the truth.
而且 你还成功地笼络了罗曼
and you manage to get Roman
七还是比六大 所以…
seven still plays six, so I'm...
我不担心
I'm not sweating it
对了 还有…
Oh, yeah, also.
根据我的消息来源
according to my sources
马特森去找了劳伦斯·易
Matsson is talking to Lawrence Yee.
沃尔特的劳伦斯?  -对
Vaulter Lawrence?   -Yeah?
所以 你知道吗  -对
So... you knew that?   -Yeah.
嘿 看啊 该死的毒蝎派对
Hey, look at this. Fuckin' scorpion party
嗨  -谁想对我出手?
Hi.  -All right, who wants a piece of me?
出一块钱 就能对人形选票出手
Pay a buck, take a pop at the human fucking vote
干脆砍下我的手吧?
Why don't I just cut my arms off?
你们一人带一只回家
I can give one to each of you to take home with
也许这样 你们就能滚了
and then maybe you'll fuck off
要喝兰姆水果酒吗
Do you want some rum punch?
对了 我在想哦…
Hey, I was... So, I was thinking.
我只是说说而已
and this is just a spitball
等这次 你们输了之后...
but when this goes through, for you guys..
还记得你们多想要“百家”吗
Remember how hot you were for The Hundred?
我能不能…
You know, could I
放弃我对IP的所有权...  -不 但是 你想得真周到
relinquish my part of the IP and...  -No, but that is very thoughtful
你要让我们去商场工作?
Wow, so, you'll like, get us a job at the mall?
让我们了解金钱的价值吗
Like, teach us the value of real money?
罗曼 别这样
Rome, come on.
我只是想实际点
I'm, like... I'm trying to be realistic about
等我上台了 就好好安排
finding nice shapes here for when I'm in there.
真好
That's nice.
确实是很好
Well, it is nice.
其实 我很希望你们两个
Yeah, actually, I would love for both of you
能支持我接手公司
to support me taking over the firm.
干吗
What?
只因为我往上爬了 孩子就要跟舅舅断绝关系?
Oh, because I'm moving forward, my kid loses access to its uncles?
是吧  -这...
Yeah?   -Well, that's
别这样 我的孩子要听谁来讲那些…
No, come on, I mean, what's it gonna do
性别歧视和恐同的笑话?
without all the... the sexist and homophobic jokes?
别想耍我们 小西
Don't fuckin' try and play us, Shiv
别再得意了
Like, stop fucking gloating
你都掐住我的脖子了
You've got your hands on my throat, yeah?
不要自以为 是韦斯达的圣女贞德
So, don't be all fuckin' Joan of Waystar.
不知道该说些什么
All right, well, I don't know what to say
你们两个可是 抢下了皇冠
'cause you... you know, you fuckin' grabbed the crown, the two of you.
爸一走 你们他妈的...
Dad died and you fucking.
联手上位 排挤我
you grabbed the crown and pushed me out.
我不懂 我怎么就成了坏蛋
So, I don't know why I'm the cunt here.
做坏事的人 就是坏蛋
Cunt is as cunt does.
了不起
Amazing.
口才太好了
Wow, Cicero on the... on the wheels of steel.
去死吧 好吗 我赢了
Fuck off. Okay? I won.
抱歉 我赢了 但我就是赢了
And I'm sorry for winning. But I did.
对不起 对不起
Sorry. I'm sorry.
知道吗 我已经不想再说对不起了
And you know what? I'm actually tired of saying fucking sorry
我棋高一着
I played it better
你们就拿出风度来 认了吧
so why don't you take it like a man and just eat it?
真是美好的向晚时分
My, what a lovely evening on the terrace.
你的鲈鱼好吃吗
How is your sea bass?
雪鱼的脸颊肉是个可敬的对手
Those... those cod cheeks were a worthy opponent, you know?
不 还不错
No, it was... it was fine.
有时我觉得 城里所有的鱼
Sometimes, I feel like every fish in this city
都是同样一块欧洲海鲈
is the same piece of xeroxed branzino, you know?
我懂. 我们可能误信了贼言
Totally. Totally, yeah, I think we may have been badly advised.
格雷格搞砸了
I think Greg fucked it. Yep
非常感谢
Merci beaucoup
要不要跟我推销一下汤姆这个人?
How would you feel about soft-pitching me? On Tom.
讲重点就好
You know, the main slide
推销我吗 要我说些留下我的好处?
On me as in my value, to keep me?
没问题 好
Sure. Yeah.
我愿意以歌换食
Yeah, I can sing for my supper.
不 那么 是的
Well, no. So, yeah.
作为一个经理人 我其实很单纯
As a manager, I think, you know, I'm... I'm simple, you know?
就是压低成本 增加收益
I squeeze the costs and juice the revenue.
跟随老板 你知道的
Follow the boss. You know?
我能消化策略 加以执行
I digest strategy and implement.
举例来说 邮轮事件
Like for, you know, Cruises, for example
重点就是吃屎和消防
was shit-gobbling and firefighting
对 泛美网科则是金钱
Yes. And ATN is money.
我负责大杀四方 和吸睛
You know, I'm cutting heads and harvesting eyeballs
其实很简单
It's pretty... Yeah, pretty simple
就是满足客户的需求
Really, I give the customer what he wants.
提供饮食上的建议并不是我的工作
I don't think it's my place to offer dietary advice.
如果他们想吃红肉和热焦油
You know, if they want red meat and boiling tar,
那我祝他们胃口大开 是吧
then buonappetito, all right?
那在耐受性方面呢 你觉得 你是什么样的人
And on a hang level? Who would you say you are?
我是什么样的人?
Who am I?
问得好
That's a good one.
我很卖命
I'm a grinder.
那是因为 我担心
I grind 'cause I worry
所有的事 都会让我 彻夜担心
I worry all night about everything
担心 对我...
All the threats to me..
对我的部门 和我本身的威胁 我…
and to my division and my physical body and I...
我非常警觉
I have an excess of vigilance, I think
很能耐受痛苦
And I have a very, very high tolerance for pain
和不舒适
and physical discomfort.
我可以老实跟你说吗 你能保密吗
Can I be frank with you? Can... can you be discreet?
当然可以
Fuck, yeah.
是这样的 跟小西…
The thing is with Shiv...
而且投票在即
and with the votes coming up and all
我们可以暂时保密
can we keep this, like, close to our chests
直到 我知道自己的票数吗  -当然
until I know my numbers?   -Oh, sure.
我觉得一切都很好 只是…
I think it's all fine. It's just, I.
我对她有点意见 就是...
I have this thing with her, which is, like..
会不会太过了点?
like, is it a bit too much?
你知道吗  -好
You know?   -Okay.
你是说漫画的事?  -不是 谁在乎漫画...
The cartoon?   -No, fuck the cartoon..
漫画还挺好笑的 我挺喜欢的 不是
That was funny. I enjoyed that. No.
在印度策略方面 她有点咄咄逼人
She was kinda pushy on the India tactics
开始 我觉得 找罗伊家族的人 有延续性
and, at first, I thought, family, continuity
可能有好处 但...
would be an upside, you know? But.
她很聪明 但...
She is... she's smart, but...
我自己有很多构想
but I got plenty of ideas, okay?
我不需要更多的构想了
I don't know if I need more ideas
我需要的是 政治上的人脉
I was in need of a little bit of the political connection, you know?
后来发现 超他妈简单的 真的
But it turns out it's fuckin' easy. It really is, you know?
加上艾芭 和其他的...
And with Ebba and blah blah blah, it's..
我什么都知道 好吗  -真的
I know everything, okay?   -You do
我想...我是说 你真的都知道
I think you... I mean, you do, man.
是的  -对
I do.  -Yeah
对
Yeah.
而且 小西 还...
Plus, with Shiv, there's also.
你知道的
You know.
她...
She...
她有点
She's somewhat..
我们有点合拍
We're a bit clickety-clickety
你懂我的意思吗
You know what I'm saying?
明白 就是...  -有一点…
Right. Like...  -A little bit..
我想上她… 有一点点想
I wanna fuck her... a little bit
我想 如果...抱歉 搞得这么尴尬
And I think under, like, sorry to get weird
但 如果情况对了...
but, like, the right circumstances.
她...我想她也会上我
She... I think she'd fuck me, too.
这会让你不自在吗 如果尴尬的话 我很抱歉
Is this making you uncomfortable? I'm sorry if it's weird
不会 我们都是男人  -是啊
No. No, we're men.  -Yeah.
我不能处理这么乱七八糟的情况
I can't deal with the mess of that, you know?
后来我又想说 我若能找世上任何一个人
So, then I was thinking, well, if I can have fuckin' anyone in the world
为什么不放弃这个大肚婆
why don't I get the guy who put the baby inside her
转而去找 把她肚子搞大的那个人呢?
instead of the baby lady?
这样的话…  -明白
It's just...  -Right.
明白
Right.
这个 我可以的
Well, I could do it.
我绝对可以 轻易上手
I could definitely, easily, definitely do it.
我需要一个美国人 免得马儿受惊
I need an American 'cause I don't wanna scare the horses
泛美网科是利润中心
ATN being the... the profit center
门肯又喜欢你
Mencken likes you,
如果他真的上位
if that happens.
你...
You know? You..
你很有才华 所以...
you're fuckin' talented. So..
而且 老实说
But also, honestly...
我找的不是合伙人
I'm not looking for a partner
而是个门面
You know? I'm looking for a frontman.
因为 我们要切肉见骨
'Cause... we're gonna cut shit close to the bone.
要真正地深入
We're gonna get right fuckin' in there.
场面会很难看
It's gonna get nasty,
所以 我需要一个肉盾…
so I need a pain sponge.
让我放手去 做我爱做的事
when I'm under the hood doing what I love, you know?
明白  -我要的 是那样的人
Sure.  -That's kinda what I'm after.
会有问题吗
So, would that be a problem?
不会 不会 找我就对了
Nah. No, man. No. I could do it
二代洛根
Logan Mark II.
不过 这代的他 很性感
Only this time, he's fuckin' sexy
太棒了 要不要喝几杯烈酒?
Yeah. Do you wanna do some shots?
要吗 好  -要 好
Can we? Yeah.  -Yes. Yeah
好  -好
Yeah.  -Yeah.
来放松一下 宝贝  -好的
Let's get a little loose, baby.  -Okay
奥斯卡
Oskar.
汤姆
Tom.
杀千刀的
Motherfucker
什么  -杀千刀的
What?   -Motherfucker.
等等 你...
What, are you... Are... Is it?
你能保住工作吗
Are you keeping your job?
我能吗?
Am I?
格雷格 我们都没事了
We're going to be okay, Greg
我们不会有事的  -到底怎样
We'll be okay.  -Which is it?
你会大幅减薪 真的 会减很多
You're gonna get castrated on pay. Like decimated
但 我想 我能留住你 好吗
But I think I can keep you. Okay?
眼睛睁大点 我先走了
Keep an eye on. Piss man out.
好
Okay.
要死了
Shit.
该死的
Fuck
格雷格瑞 嘿  -来喝一杯
Gregory! Hey! -Have a drink!
要不要喝烈酒 我们要喝烈酒
Do you want a shot? We're doing shots
那当然 要
If we're doing shots, I'll do shots.
你能喝伏特加吧
Yeah, you can handle some vodka, right?
可以  -来自祖国的烈酒
Oh, yeah.  -From the motherland
菜色很丰盛 但是分量不多
It's going to be hearty fare, but modest rations.
真让人惊讶
Surprise, surprise.
我知道 天气这么热 你们都没食欲
Well, I knew you wouldn't be hungry in this heat.
明天早餐多吃点就好了
Anyway, we can fill up on brekkie tomorrow.
去那个可怕的地方
That horrible place where...
平克·弗洛伊德的成员 好像在那里的泳池里大便过
I think someone from Pink Floyd did a poo in the swimming pool
妈 我们得回去了
Yeah, we'll need to be getting back, Mom.
真的吗  -阻止小西卖掉我们继承的遗产
Really?   -To stop Shiv selling our birthright
其实 我是要延续爸爸的计划和心愿
Well, actually, to continue on with Dad's plans and wishes.
可以不要说这些吗
Oh, please, can we just not?
我很高兴你们都来了
You know, I'm really happy to have you all here, and I..
我只想说 不管怎样
I wanted to say, for what it's worth
其实 我并不想太过问你们的事
I don't want to stick my snout in too far..
但我在想 也许 这个讨厌鬼出价购买公司
maybe, I'm wondering whether this offer from that awful man
正好给了你们一个好机会
isn't a perfect opportunity
让你们画下句点 展开人生的新章节
to, you know, say farewell, open a new chapter
我一直都是这样想的
That's always been my view.
意大利的事 你会跟我们道歉吗
Are we gonna get an apology? For Italy?
对 我是说 就某方面来说 没错
Well, yeah, I mean, in some ways, in a way, there... Yeah
她若觉得我们该卖 倒也是一以贯之
If she thinks we should sell, there's continuity.
这只是我的看法 很遗憾
It's my view and I'm sorry if you've been determined
被你们说得如此不堪
to make something squalid out of it
这是陷阱吗
Is this a set-up?
是这样吧 小西
Is that what this is, Shiv?
你想通过妈 抓住罗曼的要害
You... you trying to tie Mommy's apron strings around Romey's nuts?
什么?  -我叫彼得来
What?   -I'm going to get Peter.
我叫彼得和他朋友来 因为...
I'm going to get Peter and his friend because..
彼得  -我来了
Peter! -Coming
他和他朋友乔纳森 有个计划
His friend Jonathan and he have got a scheme
想让你们听听
they want to talk to you about
乔纳森…  -计划
and Jonathan...  -A scheme.
乔纳森是个天才
Jonathan's an absolute whiz.
只是 最近不太顺
He's just been going through some shitty stuff recently
大家好啊
Hello, hello.
这是乔纳森
This is Jonathan.
所以 这是要提案 对吧
Is this a fucking pitch? Is that what this is?
这也许感觉不太恰当 但你们的母亲...  -不会 完全不会
It might seem inappropriate, but your mother...  -No, not at all.
这也许感觉不太恰当 但不会
No, it might seem inappropriate, but it's not
因为 你们的母亲 很好心
because your mother's been kind enough
让我抢在那些秃鹫之前
to allow me to
先跟你们谈
get you before the vultures
因为 老实说 这里面的获利实在太惊人
because, frankly, the margins on this thing are just so creamy
我…
that I..
说真的 如果我不…
I honestly would feel like a terrible shit if I didn't..
一定要让你们有分一杯羹的机会
if I didn't give you the chance to come to the party
如此而已  -抱歉 失陪一下
That's all.  -Pardon me. I'll be back
这提案真的很有意思 肯  -你真的太没礼貌了
This is really interesting, Ken.  -I can't believe how rude you are
嘿 兄弟  -嘿 肯 嘿
Hey, man.  -Hey, Ken. Hey
我有大消息
So, okay, so I have something huge
兄弟 我现在置身于宇宙中心
Dude, I'm in the center of the fucking universe
我知道的事情 可以毁掉整个太阳系
with, like, knowledge to... fuckin', like, take down solar systems, man.
好 好 兄弟 很好
Sure, sure, man. That... that's great
但是...如果我给你惊人的内幕
Okay, but... if I give you something incredible
你能回报我吗
would you give me something amazing?
好啊 你要什么
Yeah, sure. Like what?
我是认真的 兄弟 真的是很惊人的内幕
Well, I'm serious, dude. It is... it is amazing
当然 所以 我也不会亏待你的
Sure, that's why I'm gonna give you something incredible
我需要
I would need.
讲白了 你们能赢吗
Basically, I get... Can... can you guys win?
你跟罗曼 如果...
You and Rome? If..
我可以跟你们成为四人组吗 货真价实的四人组
And could I quad it up? Like, full quad?
你就先说说看吧 快点说
Take your shot, buddy. Just take your shot. Come on
好 做好心理准备
Okay. Buckle up.
我们会很接近风口
Now, we're gonna be skating very close to the wind..
是的  -但是 我有绝对的信心
Yeah.  -...but I'm absolutely confident
没人… 用外行人的说法 没人能追得上我们
that no one can, well, in layman's terms, get us on this
明白
Right.
嘿 我是肯德尔 我要问你一个问题
Hey, it's Kendall. Gonna ask you a question
如果是真的 就什么都别说
If there's any veracity to it, don't say anything
明白吗
You understand?
马特森在跟别人谈
Matsson is talking to other people
重点是 我们的设施无法满足
The point is, our facilities won't offer
你对梦幻看护中心的一切需求
all that you dreamt of in a fantasy care home
但可以提供 我所谓的 扎实的基本照护
but it will afford what I call a really solid basic level of care
这也许不会是我们的选择
Not necessarily that one would like for oneself.
因为没有额外的...
You know, they're not going to offer..
不好意思 小西
Apologies. Shiv
怎么了  -我要跟你私下谈谈
What?   -I need to speak to you. In private.
也救救我吧  -抱歉 请原谅我
Can I be saved as well?   -No, sorry, guys. Please forgive me.
很抱歉 这很有意思  -罗曼 小西 拜托
Sorry, this is very captivating.  -Rome, Rome, Shiv, please, please.
你们会想听的 事关重大
You're gonna wanna hear this. It's serious.
别去太久 真是的
Don't be too late. For heaven's sakes
妈 我必须…
Mom, I need to..
乔纳森 很高兴你来了
Jonathan, I'm so glad you came.
等你们回来 鱼就变粘了
Well, the fish will just be gummy by the time you get back, it's just.
我喜欢粘粘的鱼肉  -粘粘的鱼肉
I love gummy fish.  -Gummy fish
好 这...  -怎么回事?
Okay, this is... this is...  -What?
你可能会想打电话证实…
You're... you're gonna wanna call, you'll wanna confirm
但是 我已经证实过了
but I've just had it confirmed
卢卡斯 在另外找 美国本土CEO
Lukas is interviewing for an alternative US CEO
他在搞你
He's fucking you.
放屁
Bullshit.
你怎么...  -已经证实了
How do you...  -It... it's confirmed
我有好几个消息来源
A source, a number of contacts
小西 我很遗憾  -你...
I'm sorry, Shiv.  -You...
你很遗憾? 少来了 少来了
Yeah, you're sorry? Bullshit, bullshit.
你去打电话问 我讲得没错
Call whoever. Like, it checks out
又是找劳伦斯 又常常找人出去玩
Lawrence, a bunch of vibe hangs.
有没有发现 马特森比较冷淡了 有一点吧
Have you noticed a little cooling a little bit?
先别打给马特森 我们先想想...
I wouldn't call Matsson so we can figure out.
已经打了 已经打了
Already calling, already calling
你这是狗急跳墙吧
This fuckin' desperate shit, yeah?
看到了吗
See this?
他不接你电话 有意思
Is he not answering? That's interesting
他平常会这样吗  -不会 其实很少这样
Does he... does he normally?   -No. Rarely, actually
这实在太可悲了  -什么可悲
This is so fucking pathetic.  -What's pathetic?
你啊  -好吧 对
You are.  -Okay. Fine. Yeah
如果不是真的 那我确实很可悲
I guess it would be if it wasn't true
你打去问卡洛丽娜 打给卡洛丽娜
Like, do... Call Karolina, call Karolina
新的交易声明稿中 已经没有你了
They have erased you from the new deal announcement draft
很差劲 小西 真的很差劲
It's shitty, Shiv. It... it's shitty
这是你的花招 还是真的?  -是真的
Is this fuckin' actual? Is this a move? Is this real?   -Yeah. No, it's real
格雷格说的 百分之百是真的  -操
Greg, hundred percent.  -Fuck.
那 他打算找谁?
So then, who instead?
有几个人选 劳伦斯或是克莱恩
A few faces. Lawrence, I think Klein.
不知道还有谁 但很快就会知道
I don't know who else. I'll know soon.
真是的
Man.
好吧 我是说
Okay, I mean.
所以 要让她归队吗
With her, things are... things are back?
对 只要她能调整自己的策略
As long as she can recalibrate. Yeah
混蛋
Motherfucker!
看来有搞头了
I think it's game on.
回我电话
Fucking call me back.
我想 她只是很难接受
I think it's just hard for her.
对 很明显
Yeah, that's very apparent.
这是真的
That's... that's a real thing
可恶  -对
Shit.  -Yeah.
好吧
All right, well..
所以 我们...
So, we just..
我们直接去跟她说
I think we just lay it out for her
对
Yeah.
嘿  -好的 那...
Hey.  -Okay, so...
现在怎么办
What do we do?
你跟卢卡斯谈过了吗
Well, did you talk to him? Lukas?
没有 我不想跟卢卡斯谈  -好的
No. I don't wanna talk to Lukas.  -Okay
我不想
No, I don't wanna... That I don't
他妈的 不要看我
Don't fucking look at me.
怎么了 嘿 我很遗憾
What? Hey. I'm sorry
才怪 闭嘴
No, you're not. Shut the fuck up.
我能说什么呢
Okay. What can I say?
也许什么都不能说 我们可以找人
Except maybe nothing. We might get someone
找莱尔德 或泰勒斯...
We might get Laird or Tellis.
不行 别找该死的莱尔德
No, not fucking Laird
也不要找泰勒斯
and not Tellis
我恨泰勒斯 我厌恶他 他最糟糕了
I fucking... I hate Tellis, I detest Tellis, he's the worst.
他真的很糟糕
He is the worst
打给泰勒斯 打给泰勒斯
Call Tellis, call Tellis.
我们要了解状况 打给泰勒斯
We obviously need a read. Call Tellis
但这件事绝对不能让他知道
But he's not getting even a tiny piece of this. Yeah?
这么做 你没问题吧
You okay? To do this?
这样做很难看 也很差劲 感觉很不好
This is ugly, and this is bad. It doesn't feel great
我知道 但我们是很强的组合
I know. But we're a powerful bloc
他的手法 太粗劣 太大意
Okay? It was sloppy. It was careless.
我们要宰了他
We're ready to fuckin' kill him.
我觉得 你们不切实际
Yeah, I mean, I think you're chasing rainbows
老实说 我觉得他做得滴水不漏 但 我们试试吧
To be honest, I think he has this all sewn up, but sure.
你在吗  -阿泰
You there?   -Telly
嘿  -阿泰 谢了 有收到我的短信吗
Hey.  -Telly, thanks, man. You got my message?
刚刚看到
I just saw it.
听我说 这是无损权益的朋友级简报
So, look, this is non-prejudicial. This is friend-level briefing
没有翻来覆去的法律后果
clean of upside, downside, or legal action.
副作用可能包括 天价顾问费
Side effects may include a fat fucking consultation fee.
所以… 他可能 找别人来当 美国本土CEO吗
So... so, yeah. This makes sense about US CEO?
改变决策?  -对
Him changing lanes?   -Yeah.
从他的角度来看 他需要的不是名字
I mean, from his point of view, he doesn't need the name.
而是实力
He needs chops
小西没有  -小西也在这里
And Shiv doesn't have...  -Shiv's here
去你的 泰勒斯
Fuck you, Tellis.
抱歉 小西 不 我…
Sorry, Shiv. No. I.
我只是说 如果要讨论可能的人选
I just mean in terms of the names which are being discussed
我觉得...
they make... I just..
说重点 金发弟
Cut to the chase, blondie
好 如果你们三人集体投票
Okay, if it's you three as a voting bloc
其他 还有...
and on top you have, say..
我有尤恩
I have... I have Ewan
保罗 应该还有戴维
I have Paul. I have Dewi, I think
还有斯图伊我很确定有他
And then, Stewy. Pretty sure
如果你们集体投票 应该可以形成阻止交易的威胁
I mean, as a voting bloc, you can probably threaten to kill it.
对 你们有优势
So, yeah, you have the whip hand
领导权呢 也有吗
What about leadership? Yeah?
有 你们必须对董事会提出条理清楚的计划书
Yeah, you need to present a coherent plan to the board
包括 领导人的人选
including your leadership candidate.
如果是 三人领导小组
And... and a combination or, like a trio, a troika
也可以吗
would that work or..
这个嘛…
Well.
就直说吧 别拖拖拉拉的
Just fucking say it, man. Just say.
我觉得 听起来不太可靠
I think it hasn't been great for credibility
超级胡搞兄弟乐队花车
The Incredible Fuck Brother Bandwagon
谁会叫我们超级胡搞兄弟乐队花车?
I don't know who the hell calls us The Incredible Fuck Brother Bandwagon
所有人  -真的吗
Everyone.  -Really?
你们要有统一战线 和清楚的计划
You need to look like a united front with a coherent plan
这不是亡羊补牢之计
that's not a cop-out at the fudge factory.
要有一个强而有力的CEO
One strong name for CEO
可能结合总裁的位置 或找一个有经营实力的总裁
either combined with a chair or a chair with business chops
这是我私底下的建议
Is what I would say. Off the record
谢了 阿泰 谢谢你
Thanks, Telly. Thank you
我们会再跟你讨论详细的做法
Okay, we might be in touch with some moves here, man
没问题 肯
Sounds good, Ken
我觉得 有几个可以选择的方式
I think there's a few ways through this
打电话给莱尔德 打电话给任何人 谁都可以
Call Laird. Call anyone. Honestly, anyone
任何会说 我们要在国王的带领下
Anyone would say we have to go into battle
跟自己口中的未来对抗的人
with our own version of the future, with a king
请问 你有属意的人选吗
Oh, and pray tell, do you have one in mind?
马特森是个小人
Matsson's a fuckin' prick. Right?
他基本上害死了爸爸 硬逼着爸去找他
He practically killed Dad, dragging him over.
他善变 无情 不懂这个行业
He's capricious, he's cold, he doesn't understand the business.
他是个混账
He's a prick.
我想杀了他
I would like to kill him.
如果想杀他 我们得实际一点
And if we're gonna kill him, we need to get real
我们需要
And we would need.
我想 应该是我 对吧
I think it would be me, right?
这个嘛
Well..
爸说应该是我
Dad said that it would be me.
什么时候说的
When?
我们的感情后来变好了
Well, we were getting close again before
你们也差不多都知道
and you know this, mostly
我有跟他传短信 他对我很和蔼
And I was texting, and he was warm
有一天深夜 我跟他在一起时 他说 接班人应该是...
and he said when I was with him late one night that it should be..
真有说服力
Persuasive
他在四下无人时还说了什么
What else did he say when no one was around?
说他是黄道十二营杀手? 图派克也是他杀的?
That he was the Zodiac Killer? That he did Tupac?
随便啦 我说的是真的
Whatever. It's fuckin'... I said it, it's true, and
对 管他的 随你们爱怎么做
Yeah. Fuck it. Do whatever you want with that.
我说的是真的
It's just the fuckin' truth.
他也找过我接班 罗曼
Well, he offered it to me, too, Rome.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
他...
He...
他承诺要让我接班
he fuckin' promised it to me
他承诺了我 七岁时
Promised. When I was seven.
他叫我坐下来 在布里治汉普顿的糖果厨房
He sat me down at the Candy Kitchen in Bridgehampton
承诺要让我接班
and he fuckin' promised it to me.
我七岁的时候
Seven years old
你们能想象吗
Like, can you imagine?
对啦
Yeah.
有图有真相
Pics or it didn't happen.
那...很过分
That was... messed up.
他不该那么做的
Like, he shouldn't have done that.
对 他不该那么说
No. He shouldn't have said that.
我的意思是 他说过的话很多
I'm simply saying he said a lot of things..
而且都是先跟我说的
and he said them to me first
但是 是最后跟我说的
Yeah, and he said it to me last.
你想当CEO吗
Do you even want it?
因为...葬礼的时候
Because... at the funeral, yeah?
你不是那种人
Like, you're... you're not that guy.
你不是...  -什么
You're not...  -What?
你镇不住场面
You couldn't... do the rounds
你...  -我怎么了?
I mean, you kinda...  -Well, what?
你怯场了 那…
.shrank into yourself, I mean, that.
就因为 我他妈 在父亲的葬礼上 哭了一会吗
What? 'Cause I, like, fuckin'... I cried a little at my father's funeral?
就表示 我一辈子就毁了吗?
That means I'm totally fucked forever?
感觉不太对啊
That doesn't seem right
那当然不代表你是坏人
It absolutely does not make you a bad person.
你没有在葬礼上图谋不轨
Like, maybe it makes you a good person
代表你是好人
that you weren't snaking at the funeral.
也许你人格健全
Like, maybe... maybe you're well-adjusted
而我 是商界的变态
and I'm a business psycho
我也不知道 这是…
I don't know, man. It... like..
这是一份很可怕的工作 显然会让你很煎熬
It's... it's a fuckin' horrible job that clearly kills you
所以 我…
So I'm just.
说真的 我只是想带大家往前走
Honestly, I'm just trying to guide us through the years
找到真相
to some truth here, man.
太好了 好老套
Great. Yeah. Cheesy.
我是说真的
I'm serious
是啊 你是真的好老套
Yeah. A serious fuckin' cheeseball is what you are.
他只是说不出口
He just can't say it.
他也不想 但是说不出口
He doesn't want it, but he can't say it
那我呢
And me?
我爱你 小西 我真的很爱你
I love you, Shiv. I fucking love you
但 我们不能进去说
But we simply cannot walk in there
要阻止跟他的交易
and say we're blocking his offe
说我们对未来有美好的愿景
and we have this compelling vision
领导人是你
and say that leading it is you
而你 昨天还在帮马特森
when yesterday, you were singing his song
我们不能这样做
We simply can't.
我们也不能说是罗曼
And we can't say it's Roman
因为他没有分量 看起来很可怜
because he lacks heft and he looks pathetic
而且可能崩溃 所以
and he might flop, so.
我当然希望是我
Obviously, I want it to be me.
但我真心觉得
But I genuinely think anyone would say
任何 立场客观的人 都会说
anyone objectively would say
洛杉矶 我的简历 我的经验
LA, my profile, experience
职位 意图 公开宣言...
position, desire, public pronouncements.
非我莫属
it's me.
如果想为我们留下这家公司
If we wanna hold on to this company, for us
为我的小孩 你的小孩…
for my kids, for yours.
非我莫属
it's me.
嘿 罗曼  -怎样
Hey, Rome.  -Yeah.
你猜 肯德尔觉得应该选谁
Guess who Kendall thinks it should be.
你一定会大吃一惊的
It's gonna blow your fuckin' mind
好的...  -我们可以找出一个很酷的架构
Okay..."-We can find a cool structure.
像封邑或王国
Right? Like fiefdoms, kingdoms
如果反将那个维京人一军 这可是很大的成就
We pull off a reverse Viking, guys? Like, it's fuckin' huge.
小西 真的 泛美网科和新闻部都给你
Shiv, seriously, take ATN, take all of news
你去拯救世界
save the world.
罗曼 社群媒体归你
Rome, social media
再恶整一通 一定会很好玩
fuck it all up again, it'll be fun.
我们不是真的要下水吧 因为 你知道...
We aren't actually going in, right? 'Cause, you know.
这里没有坏鲨鱼 它们都在北大西洋
There's no bad sharks in Bim, baby. They're North Atlantic
它们可以往返两地
Well, they could commute
如果你不知道 所有的海洋
All the seas, in case you didn't know this
都是相通的
are connected
对于想吃我的动物来说 海洋就是水底地铁
It's like a huge water subway for things that wanna eat me.
来 我们下水 来啦
Come on, let's do it. Come on
我们也要?
Should we?
对  -好吧
Yeah.  -Okay.
可以等我们一分钟吗
Can you give us a minute?
也许
Maybe.
所以呢
So?
我们可以不管了 脱身
We could fuck it. Get out
卖给马特森 让...
Sell to Matsson, let..
劳伦斯或其他商学院毕业生
Lawrence or some other business-school dry cleaner
坐上王座
sit in the throne
关门大吉 拱手让人
Shut up shop and give away the keys
不过 不能是他
It can't be him, though
也绝对不能是你
But it really can't be you
好吧 我恨他 但是很怕你
Well, okay, I hate him, but I fear you
他会让人无法忍受 你会是一场大灾难
He would be unbearable, and you would be a disaster.
他会...
He'd be...
一定会很可怕 真的
It will be terrible. It will
但 很不幸的 我还是勉强可以接受
But... I don't know. I can sort of, unfortunately, see it
不过 你嘛…
Whereas you..
马特森很重视我
Matsson took me seriously
或是他把你当傻子耍
Or he played you like a big fiddle
当成 一个大腹便便的傻子
Like a pregnant cello
抱歉
Sorry.
你觉得 爸会想让谁接班?
Who do you think Dad actually wanted to give it to?
我觉得 爸爸除了往前冲之外
I don't think Dad gave a fuck about anything
什么都不在乎
more than putting one foot in front of the other.
对 我认为 他不想让我们任何一个人接班
Yeah, I don't think he wanted to give it to any of us
是啊  -我不知道
Yeah.  -I don't know.
我们可以让给他
We could give it to him.
对 也许我们该这么做
Yeah. We probably should
除非...  -除非什么
Unless...  -Unless?
除非我们杀了他  -好的 杀了他
Unless we kill him.  -Okay. Kill him
是的  -我喜欢
Yeah.  -I like that.
有意思  怎么杀
That's intriguing. How'd we do it?
胡闹过了头
Well, just a bit of horseplay gone wrong
打他的头 用椰子敲他的脑袋
Just a biff to the head then a bonk on the noggin with a coconut
等他全身瘫软 一报还一报
Wait 'til he goes limp. What goes around comes around?
对 杀了他 我们就能去睡觉了
Yeah, and if we kill him, we get to go to bed.
我好累
I'm tired.
但 如果没成功 他会很烦
He'd be so annoying if it went wrong
我是说 没杀成
The murdering? Like..
你们刚刚是不是想杀我?
"Did you just try to murder me?
这实在不是你们该做的事
Dude, that is so not actually what you meant to do
而且 这样也不好
and it is not a good thing to do."
你们刚刚杀了我 真的很差劲
"You guys actually just murdered me. You guys are the worst
你们好大的胆子
How dare you?"
所以 要吗  -对 对
Shall we?   -Yeah, yeah
嘿 我们想杀你
Hey. So, we were thinking of murdering you
别告诉他啊
Well, don't tell him
但是 准备功夫太多了
But you know, it's too much prep
行政作业太麻烦
Too much murder admin
我最讨厌行政作业
No stomach for the admin.
所以....  -好的
So...  -Okay
我们封你为王
We anoint you
弄臣的权杖给你
You get the bauble.
恭喜
Congratulations
权杖有鬼 被谊咒了 而且诸事不吉
It's haunted and cursed and nothing will ever go right
但是...权杖是你的了
but... yeah, enjoy your bauble
是吗  -对
Yeah?   --Yeah
谢谢
Thank you.
你看他的表情
Look at his face.
是啊  -小贱人 你可以笑
Yeah.  -You can smile, bitch
这样才对嘛  -他笑了
Yeah, there we go.  -There you go
露点牙齿来瞧瞧  -肯开心了
Show some goddamn teeth.  -Happy Ken
肯开心了  -肯开心了
Happy Ken.  -Happy Ken
开心的肯就是这个样子  -好怪
Yeah, that's what happy Kendall looks like.  -Weird
如果我们要封他为王 他必须完成一个任务
If we're going to anoint him, he needs to complete a task
对 像是 上楼悄悄地说…
Yeah. Like walk upstairs and say real quietly.
嘿 乔纳森 我想跟你说句话
"Hey, Jonathan, I'd like a word with you.
跟我的屁眼说吧
In my ass."
说的时候 嘴里要含看一匙肉桂粉
And say it with a spoonful of cinnamon in your mouth
已经做过了
Oh, that's been done.
李·艾柯卡接手福特的时候已经做过了
That's what they made Lee Iacocca do when he took over at Ford
罗曼  -干吗
Rome.  -What?
国王吃的大餐?
Meal fit for a king?
对
Yes.
我们要帮你做一顿国王吃的大餐 所以...
We are gonna make you a meal fit for a king, so.
太好了  -好丰富的食材 好的
Yes, sir.  -What a mighty bounty. All right
里面有做三明治的东西吗
Is there actually anything in there for a sandwich?
我好饿  -有
I'm starving.  -Yes.
妈咪有两颗发芽的土豆
Mommy with hair-sprouting potatoes
脱脂牛奶 和战争期间的酸黄瓜
zero-percent milk, and wartime pickle
妈妈真是宠坏我们了
You do spoil us so.
恶心的东西
Something gross.
你会是一个很优秀的CEO
Oh, you... you know, you're gonna be a great CEO
我真的这么觉得
I really think that.
如果这个没有害死你的话 但我觉得肯定会
If this doesn't kill you, which it definitely will
所以...  -我超饿
So...  -Well, I'm actually starving.
这个好像过期了
And I think this is expired, so..
这是辣酱
This is a hot sauce.
牛奶吗 这是很好的开胃菜  -牛奶
Milk? Oh, it's a great starter.  -Milk.
国王吃的大餐.
Meal fit for a king..
全部喝下去宝贝...  -安静
Chuck it in, don't know...  -Quiet..
你们全都回来了  -抱歉
I see you all came back.  -Sorry..
怎么回事  -嗨 我们…
What's going on?   -Hi, we're...
国王吃的大餐  -在做一顿国王吃的大餐
Meal fit for a king.  -making a meal fit for a king
是吗 可以小声地做吗  -我是国王
Yeah? But can you do it quietly?   -I'm the king.
因为 乔纳森在楼上睡觉
'Cause, you know, Jonathan's trying to get to sleep upstairs
你们的无礼 让他大受打击
He's trying to recover after your rudeness.
抱歉  -人家大老远
Sorry.  -Hey, he came all the way
从摩纳哥过来 他在这里待的时间不多
from Monaco, he has to watch his days here.
我们在庆祝
We're... we're celebrating
不是庆祝 是哀悼
We're not celebrating. We're mourning
我们想杀他
We're trying to kill him
我们为了保住公司 要集体投票
We're voting as a bloc. Together. To keep the firm
真是 天杀的
Blimey O'Reilly
天啊
Oh, gosh.
那就你担下来吧
Well, on your head be it
我得到一些坏消息
Well, I had some negative news
所以 我们友善地讨论了
and so then we decided to have a friendly conversation
要让谁上位
about who should... who it would be
我们现在必须册封他 因为这是对待国王的方式
Now we have to anoint him because that's what you do to a king.
随你们 但这会毁了圣诞节吧
Fine. That fucks Christmas up, doesn't it?
别碰那个 那是彼得的芝士
And don't touch that. That's Peter's cheese
真是够了
God's sake.
我自己也犯过这样的错误
I made that mistake myself.
那种芝士对他很特别 乱动他会发火的
It's his special cheese. He gets really boring about it
母亲 你家食物不多
Mother, there... there really isn't much food..
这样吧 彼得不喜欢硬皮
I'll tell you what, Peter doesn't like the knobbies
所以 我都放冷冻库
So I freeze them.
他不喜欢什么?  -就是硬皮啊
He doesn't like the what?   -You know, the knobbies
吐司两头的地方  -这样啊
The loaf ends.  -Okay
请慢用  -是一整袋冷冻硬皮
Enjoy.  -Oh, it's a bag of frozen knobbies
发挥一下创意啊
Oh, well, look, you know, be inventive.
其实 我很高兴你们能和睦相处
Do you know, I'm actually quite glad that you're getting along so well
彼得会很失望
I mean, Peter will be disappointed
但 很高兴看到你们能有共识
but, you know, it's nice to see you've got something to agree about
除了 一致觉得我是个很糟的母亲之外
besides what a terrible mother I am
妈 那一点 是我们不变的共识
Oh, well, we'll never disagree on that, Mom.
对  -我知道
Yeah.  -Oh, I'm sure
晚安  -我们爱你
Nighty-night.  -We love you
我也爱你们  -妈妈我爱你
Yeah, I love you, too.  -I love you Mama
晚安
Night-night
我要吃他的芝士  -“彼得
I'm gonna eat his cheese.  -"Peter doesn't like
不喜欢硬皮 亲爱的”
the knobbies, darling
你才是硬皮 你才是硬皮
You're a knobbie, you're a knobbie.
接住  -你是硬皮
Catch it.  -You're a knobbie.
一连三个 你是怎么办到的
Okay, now three in a row? How do we do that?
不要吃彼得的芝士
Don't eat Peter's cheese.
乔纳森 乔纳森在睡觉
Jonathan. Jonathan's sleeping.
抱歉 彼得  -不要舔彼得的芝士
Sorry, Peter.  -Don't lick Peter's cheese.
天啊 不要舔彼得的芝士  -天啊 好恶心
Oh, God, don't lick Peter's cheese.  -Oh, my God. That is so gross.
对不起 妈咪
I'm so sorry, Mommy
不要用嘴碰彼得的宝贝芝士
Don't go down on Peter's special cheese.
我是用手帕包着拿过来的 罗曼
I brought that over in a hankie, Rome.
对不起 妈咪 我全舔过了
I'm so sorry, Mommy. I licked it all over.
对不起 妈咪 我舔了你的芝士
I'm so sorry, Mommy. I licked the cheese.
我忍不住一直舔 太对不起了
I can't stop licking his cheese. I'm so sorry.
小声点
Let's keep it quiet.
加一点辣酱
A little Tabasco.
加一大堆辣酱
A lot of Tabasco.
这真是...快好了
Now, this is really... We're so close
布兰斯顿...太好了
Branston... Oh, yeah
布兰斯顿酸黄瓜 你的最爱
Branston pickle. You love that.
快好了 没做过这样的
We're so close. Never got there.
可以了
Yeah, we're good
我觉得可以了
I think this is good
这是有益健康的补品
No, this is a healthful tonic
真的非常好
This is really good
给国王吃的大餐
Meal fit for a king
等一下...
Yeah, wait...
我不喝
I'm not actually drinking that
给国王吃的大餐
Meal fit for the king!
不 不要
No, no, don't do that
干杯
Drink up.
会没事吧
This is gonna be all right, right?
我是说 我们会没事?
Like... we're all right?
对吧  -快点喝就对了
Yeah?   -Just fucking drink it.
天啊
Oh,God.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
国王不戴套帽子
Kings don't wear silly hats
只戴王冠  -我喝不下了
Kings wear crowns.  -I can't drink anymore.
那就别喝 戴上你的王冠
Well, then, don't. Wear your crown, sir.
不  -不 不
Oh, no.  -No... no.
不要.  -你的王冠 戴上你的王冠
No... no.  -Your crown. Wear your crown
不要...  -不要...
No...  -No...
我帮你戴...  -不要
Then let me crown...  -No.
天啊 妈  -国王
Oh, my God. Mom! -King!
再见 妈妈 再见 亲爱的
Bye, Mom.  -Okay. Bye, darling
谢谢你的眼药水
Thanks for the... the props
我有一些生意
We'll do some business.
再见  -再见
Yeah, bye.  --Bye.
再见  -很高兴看到你
Bye.  -Good to see you.
快滚吧
Go away.
真是浪费时间
What a complete fucking waste of time.
最好放手让尤恩去做
I mean, yeah, I... I think Ewan is best just left to it
我不知道 我不知道有没有时间 康
I don't know if there's time, Con.
好的 他跟我在一起 我们刚落地
All right. I have him here with me. We just landed
老朋友保罗 是的 他不会那样做的 对吧
Good ol' Paul, yeah, he don't do that, right?
是 我随时可以去找斯图伊
Yeah, I'll...I'll go wherever, whenever for Stewy.
保罗会挺我们 他不信任科技
Paul's good. Paul's rock. He doesn't trust tech.
老朋友保罗  -康纳想知道
Good old Paul.  -Connor wants to know
我们会不会做资产再配置
if we're gonna make the Great Reallocation?
我们在乎吗 我们想要这么做吗
Oh, I mean, do we care? Do we want to?
弗兰克和卡尔会到吗
Are Frank and Karl gonna be there?
因为他们可能...  -不知道
'Cause it could be...  -Don't know
不知道  -我们要不要
I don't know.  -  Okay, could we just do..
我们先去爸爸家躲一下
We're gonna hide out at Dad's
他好像要发疯了…
He's kinda losing this shit, so.
就这么干吧 就去做资产再配置
Let's do it. To the Great Reallocation.
出发吧  -好 出发
Let's go.  -Okay, off we go
我们会到的 对  -去参加狗屁古董大混战
We'll be there. Yeah.  --To the fuckin' Antiques Shitshow!
戴维
Dewi!
你好吗  -还不错
How are you?   -I'm good
去我爸爸家  -没问题
To my dad's.  -Got it.
我知道 你们很多人
I know that many of you
下午还有重要的安排
have somewhere rather important to be this afternoon
但 这个系统很简单
But the system is pretty simple
请各位 以顺时钟方向 在公寓中移动
So, as you move in a clockwise direction around the apartment
看到喜欢的东西 就贴上贴纸
affix your stickers to objects you covet
有些东西只能贴一张贴纸
One sticker each on a number of different articles
大家都喜欢的 可以贴好几张
or many on one prized item.
之后 前来的哀悼的人
Okay, so subsequent circulating mourners
可以贴上他们的贴纸
will then apply their stickers.
环绕公寓两周之后...
After two stickering perambulating circuits
简称SPC  -好的
We call them SPCs.  -Okay.
物件会被分配给 出价较高的贴贴纸者
...objects will be assigned to the highest sticker bidder.
如果出价不相上下
Where sticker claims are tied
就进入决胜的贴纸回合
we move on to the tie-break stickering perambulation circuit.
简称TBSPC
TBSPCs
之后 所有没有贴贴纸的物件 会被集中起来
After which, all unstickered items will be pooled and distributed
按反向字母顺序分配
in reverse alphabetical order
除了被第二级...
other than those stickered by the second tier
抱歉 遗族贴上贴纸的
excuse me, bereaved.
这样讲 清楚吗
Do I make myself clear?
很清楚 这个系统非常好 康
Absolutely. It's a good system, Con.
那就开始吧 去贴贴纸
All right, it's on. Go get 'em
这个真不错
Oh, that's nice.
游戏开始  -嘿 康 那些勋章呢
Game on.  -Hey, Con. Where are the medals?
那个...其实已经进行过一回合了
Yeah, there was a... first round.
最初的一回合结束了
There was... an initial round
那一回合有谁来?
And who was present at that?
就只有我
That was myself.
一个人  -行
Solely.  -Right.
这些都要卖掉吗
Okay, and does all of this have to go?
你不要...
I mean, you don't wanna...
我希望全部都清空
Well, I'd like to get rid of pretty much everything
我有一些很棒的东西要送进来
I have some pretty cool stuff coming in
有一张这么长的奶牛纹沙发
like a cow print couch about, like, yea long
太好了 康 你不想多留一些吗
Great. Con? You don't wanna keep more for..
我们的计划是 如果...当门肯就职
Well, we're planning on if... when Mencken comes through
我们要做个尝试
we're actually experimenting with an idea..
我六到八个月后要读剧...
I have a play reading in six to eight months.
康要去斯洛文尼亚 那个 我也要忙
and Con is going to Slovenia and I'll be working on that
所以 我们要试着…
so we're gonna try...
对 我们...很期待
Yeah, you know, we're... we're really excited
让分隔两地
how this long-distance thing
不要那么无趣
can add another dimension, you know, to..
对 多点情趣
Yeah, add a little spice, you know?
为婚姻生活加点料
As we, you know, get deeper into the marriage.
好 火辣
Yeah, that's sexy
这好像叫“两周之痒”
They call that the second-week itch, I believe.
罗曼  -怎样
Rome.  -Yeah.
我们很期待  -是
We're excited.  -Yeah.
威斯康辛法院的事 有最新消息吗
Head the latest about the Wisconsin court thing?
对不起 什么法院的事?
I'm sorry, what court thing?
一个小问题
It's a hiccup.
对杰瑞德来说 只是个小问题
Just a little hiccup for Jeryd, I think
了解  -对
Okay.  -Yeah.
也许 门肯无法当选
I mean, maybe Mencken might not make it
也许 你们不用分隔两地了
and so, maybe you might get to keep him all to yourself.
太好了
Great.
我要这把拆信刀
I think I'm gonna take this letter opener.
这是什么鬼
What the fuck is this?
跟老爸的虚拟晚餐
Virtual dinner with Pop.
什么
What?
这是什么时候拍的  -我不知道 是几周前
When is this from?  ?   -I don't know how many weeks ago
好 来吧
Okay, here we go.
高尔 杜尔 布什
Gore, Dole, Bush.
他也在列选输的名单吗
Is he doing the... Wait, the loser's list?
对  -孟岱尔 卡特 福特
Yeah.  -Mondale, Carter, a Ford
他不是林肯
Not a Lincoln for me.
嬉皮乔治 汉弗莱 圣伯瑞
Hippie George, Humphrey, St. Barry.
坏胚子狄克
Dick the Bad,
威尔基 兰登 胡佛 梵谛冈的阿尔·史密斯
Wilke, Landon, Hoover, Al Smith of the Vatican
大卫·考克斯 休斯 塔夫特
David Cox, Hughes, Taft
布莱恩 马丁 范布伦
Bryan, Martin Van Buren
怀特 威廉·亨利 哈里森 克莱
White, Old Tippecanoe, Clay
约翰·昆西·亚当斯
Hey, JQA.
你今天输了...  -你今天输了...
How many elections...  -How many elections..
…几场选举?  -…几场选举?
have you lost today?   -have you lost today?
第一个克林顿
Clinton the First..
但不是最烂的  -但不是最烂的
But not the worst.  -but not the worst.
平克尼两次 杰弗逊 亚当斯 都很好
Pinckney twice. Jefferson, Adams, all very nice.
真不敢相信 他还记得
I can't believe he can still do that.
好 下一个换谁 格丽?  -好
All right, who's next? Gerri?   --Yeah.
念那首打油诗 格丽 念那首打油诗
Do the limerick. Gerri, do the limerick
对  -比我的财宝更重要的
Yeah.  -Much dearer to me than my treasure
女继承人说 是我的自由
The heiress declared, is my leisure
因为 那样 我可以搞整个哈佛团队
For then I can screw The whole Harvard crew
他们动作很慢 但可以延长欢愉
They're slow But that lengthens the pleasure.
好  -康纳
Yeah.  -Connor!
好...
All right, okay...
各位 女士先生 我要表演 “我是个小茶壶”
I give you, ladies and gentlemen, I am a little teapot.
很好 用洛根·罗伊先生的方式表演
Oh, good one.  -In the manner of Mr. Logan Roy
好 来看看吧  -我的天啊
Very good. Let's see it.  -Oh, my God
表演开始  -我是个小茶壶
Showtime.  -I am a little teapot
滚开
Fuck off!
我是茶壶 矮又肥 你说我是什么?
Short and stout. What did you fuckin' call me?
这是壶柄 这是嘴
Here's my handle. Here's my fuckin' spout.
我冒烟时 你能听到我大吼
When I get steamed up, you can hear me shout.
弗兰克·弗农是个白痴 卡尔·马勒是个德国佬
Frank Vernon is a moron, Karl Muller is a Kraut!
太像了
That was incredible.
老爸不喜欢
Pop did not like it.
爸 你怎么能不喜欢呢
Pop, how could you not?
很有创意  -打他的脸
It's creative.  -Hit him in his face
好了 卡尔 来唱吧 唱吧
All right, Karl. Come on, sing it. Sing it
到时拷贝给我一份  -快唱
I want a copy of this. Sing it.
♪思虑重重♪    -要拷给我一份
♪There's naught but care on every hand♪   -I'd like to have it.
没问题
I got it.
♪流逝的每一个小时♪
♪ In every hour that passes, O ♪
♪女人定义了一个男人的生命♪
♪ What signifies the life o' man and 'twere not for the lassies, O ♪
卡尔 你唱得好烂
You're murdering it, Karl.
♪青青灯心草♪
♪Green grow the rashes, O ♪
♪我与女人共度♪
♪The sweetest hours that 'ere I spend♪
♪我最美好的时光♪
♪ Are spent among the lassies♪
凯莉 你听他唱得好烂
Kerry, listen, he's murdering it
他唱得好烂
He's murdering it
♪追逐财富的竞赛♪
♪The worldly race may riches chase♪
♪财富仍可能逃离♪
♪ And riches still may fly them, O ♪
♪虽然他们抓到了财富力♪
♪And even though they catch 'em fast♪
♪但永远无法享用♪
♪ Their hearts can ne'er enjoy 'em, O ♪
♪青青灯心草♪
♪ Green grow the rashes, O ♪
♪我与女人共度了♪
♪The sweetest hours that e'er I spent ♪
♪我最美好的时光♪
♪Were spent among the lassies, O ♪
对
Hey. Yeah.
还好吗
Doing okay?
你不会被炒鱿鱼
You're not gonna get canned?
应该 应该不会
I don't... I don't... I don't think so.
但...
But...
祝你好运
Good luck.
不
No.
不用了
No, no.
不用了 那个没戏了
No, that's all fucked.
是吗  -对
Yeah?   -Well, yeah
对 马特森只是在要我
I mean, Matsson was just stringing me along
不然 就是改变心意了 但你知道...
or he switched lanes, but you know, it's..
不管怎样 出线的绝对不会是我
Either way, it's not gonna be me.
对啊
Yeah.
好...你确定吗
Okay. I did... Are you sure?
那...怎么...
mean, is that? How? What did... did.
那 是真的吗  -对 格雷格说的
Is that even true?   -Yeah. Greg.
对
Yeah
天啊 天啊 真是没想到
Man, oh, man, Man, oh man. What a thing.
那...太糟了
That's... that's terrible.
你觉得他...
So, like, who do... who do you think he would.
我是说 那 又会是谁呢
I mean, who would it be? Like.
不知道 可能是某个...
I don't know. Like, a..
科技界的红人 劳伦斯吧
tech pal, big hitter. Lawrence, maybe.
可恶  -对啊
Fuck.  -Yeah.
他可以去死
Well, fuck him.
对 也许你该...
Yeah. Well, 'maybe..
也许 你该投赞成票 如果都已经成定局的话
Maybe you should vote it through, you know, if it's all set.
我也不知道
I don't know.
什么  -不是...
What?   -Yeah? No, no, I just...
不 我只是想说 如果...
No, I was just thinking if it was..
不是啦
No, no.
小西 也许该让你知道
Yeah, Shiv, you should probably know...
是我
it's me.
是你?
It's you?
对啊 不如就告诉你吧
Yeah, you might as well know.
你反正...  -放屁
I mean, you're gonna find...  -Bullshit.
你反正很快就会知道...我想...
mean, you're gonna find out. It's gonna be, I think
对 我…
Yeah. And I...
我在想 也许...
You know, maybe... maybe I wonder if you..
你该支持...
if it is an idea that you should..
你去死啦 是真的吗?
Oh, fuck you. Really?
操你妈
Fuck you.
对  -什么?
Yeah.  -What?
你...
You...
天啊 你真他妈...
Jesus, you're a fuckin'..
他居然 找了个空心傀儡?
Like, he went for a... an empty-fucking suit?
是啦 也许你该投赞成票
"Oh, yeah, maybe, oh, actually, you should vote it through
也许吧
Hey, yeah, maybe."
别这样 我了解你
Come on. I know you
易地而处 你也会这么做的
Like you wouldn't if it was the other way around?
知道吗 我祝你好运
You know what? Good luck. Yeah?
祝你好运 狗娘养的
Good luck, motherfucker
因为 我们票数够了
Cause we have the numbers. Yeah?
祝你狗日的好运
Good fucking luck
是汤姆
It's Tom.
什么  -是该死的汤姆
What?   -It's fucking Tom
汤姆?
Tom?
走吧 我们走吧
Yeah. Let's go.
我们走吧 去算一下我们的票数
Let's fucking go. Let's run our numbers
走  -天啊 结果被干洗店整了
Let's go.  -Man. Fucked by the dry cleaner.
嘿 格雷格 借一步说话 好吗
Hey, Greg. Can I have a word?
跟你聊几句 现在聊
A word, yeah? Just... just right now?
可以吗 是公事 要谈策略
Do you mind? Corporate matter. Tactical
嗨 汤姆  -嘿
Hi, Tom.  -Hey
回头见
See you.
进来这里谈
Yeah, just in here.
洗手间?  -对啊
In the bathroom?   -Sure.
好  -快点
Yeah.  -Come on.
你 说出去了?
Did you tell?
什么  -你是不是给说出去了?
What?   -Did you fucking tell?
你这个混蛋 我就差这么一点
You bastard. I was this close.
现在 他们有机会 他妈的
And now they have a chance to fucking pull
绝地大反攻了 你这个混蛋
their fucking opposition together, you fucking prick
不对 我觉得 我没...
No, I.. Look, I don't think..
你这个天杀的贱人
You fucking little prick
你这个烂货...
You fucking little piece of... shit
去你的
Fuck you!
有问题了 有大问题了
Problem. Big fucking problem.
僵尸快醒醒
All right, wake up, zombies!
该动起来了 快点
Time to activate! Come on!
电话 我要看到电话
Phones! I wanna see some fuckin' phones!
弗兰克呢 我们得找到弗兰克
And where's Frank? We get ahold of Frank.
打电话给弗兰克 确定他不会跑票
Call Frank, call Frank... Make sure he's locked in
好的 艾芭呢
Okay. Where's Ebba?
艾芭
Ebba!
斯图伊?  -还摇摆不定
Stewy?   -Yeah, a wobble.
他是个摇摆不定的混蛋  -好的
He's a wobbly fucking bastard.  -Okay
好 那去找他 给他点颜色瞧
Okay. Well, let's go get him. Let's fuck him up.
庭院一片寂静
Silence in the courtyard
街上也是一片寂静
Silence in the street.
全英国最大的蠢蛋要说话了?
The biggest fool in England is just about to speak?
我去我的办公室  -好
I'm gonna go to my office.  -All right.
克蕾儿 有我的留言吗  -嗨
Claire, do you have any messages?   -Hi
嘿  -你还好吗
Hey.  -How you doing?
你们能阻止交易吗
You'll be able to block, do you think?
太好了 我觉得太棒了
Great. I think that's great
正好可以改变一下文化 终结暗箭伤人的做法
A chance to change the culture of backstabbing
展开一个新的纪元 我在想…
a new era, and I was wondering..
就是天下大乱之前 我们私下聊聊
Just between us and before, you know, things blow up
也许 改变的一部分 是让雨果走
maybe part of that change is getting rid of Hugo
我只是 想提出我的想法而已
I just wanted to plant the seed, that's all
早安
Mornin', mornin'
恭喜
Congrats.
谢了
Yeah, thanks.
看来 他们听说
Well, looks like they've heard
自己的蛋蛋可能着火了  -是啊
their testicles might be on fire.  -Yeah
我从来没看过弗兰克跑得那么快
I haven't seen Frank run like that ever.
我们可以 帮忙做 事前准备吗
Okay, can we help prepare the ground?
到时候 场面会很难看 所以 是的
Well, it's gonna be a fairly explosive mega-fuck, so yeah
GoJo的交易会破产
The GoJo deal is gonna die
弗兰克可能会反悔
Frank maybe pulls the vote
或他们硬于 搞得灰头土脸
or they push and get humiliated
所以 要
So, yeah.
今天是生产线的大日子 对吧
Big, big day on the old salami line, huh?
完全正确
Yeah, it sure is. Yeah.
我给你素材  -好的
I'll get you the materials.  -Okay
财务细节
Details on the financing
日报专访的背景资料
for background for... for the Journal piece.
是的 那是...  -请便
Yeah, it's...  -Yeah. Whatever.
那又不是魔法椅 坐吧
It's not a magic chair. Yeah, go ahead
好的...  -嘿...情况如何
Okay...  -Hey... How're we lookin'?
嘿 兄弟 我们会赢的
Hey, dude. We have it.
好吗 我们会赢的
Okay? We have it.
你会帮我们吗 你会帮我们吧?
But do we have you? We've got you, right?
我对 坐蔬菜专车 还是有些质疑
Well, I do have certain questions about riding the vegetable train
但 我是个自私的人 所以...
But, like, I am a selfish person, so..
要邀请斯图锅吗
Do we invite the Stewpot in?
要让他进来吗
You know, get him inside?
不坐主管的椅子
Non-exec chair.
专走后门的运动人士
Fuckin' activist backtivist
椅子? 各位...
Chair? Guys.
我喜欢怪异的性爱 喜欢嗑烂药
I like weird sex, I like bad drugs.
我是个很复杂的人
I'm a very complicated individual
放屁
Bullshit.
放屁 你喜欢煎饼和松饼
Bullshit, you like pancakes and waffles
嗑了快乐丸 会跟男人接吻
and you kiss guys on Molly
你不是黑暗之心
You're not the heart of darkness
是长了根小老二的 烤芝士三明治
You're a... you're a grilled cheese with a sucked dick
让我们帮你打理一下形象
Let us clean you up
我们考虑一下吧
Well, why don't we just think about it, huh?
小西...
And, Shiv...
我觉得 如果抓桑蒂一把
you know, I do think if we give Sandi a little tug
她可能会动摇
she might be somewhat foldable
好 太好了 我们走
Okay. Great. Perfect, let's go
你做得很好 兄弟
And you did a fucking good one, man.
是吗
Yeah?
斯图锅主席 我喜欢 小西 你喜欢吗
Chairman Stewpot, I'm into that. Are you into that, Shiv?
嘿 她来做什么  -这边请
Hey, what's she doing in?   -Shall we?
谁  -格丽来做什么
Who?   -Gerri. What's she doing here?
不知道 但我想
I don't know, I think.
我们付了她天价 所以 她还能进来吧
we're paying her off big time, so it's not a lockout, right?
我不想看到她 她该来吗
I don't... I don't wanna see her. Should she even be around?
好 我们赶她走
Yeah, sure. Let's... let's fuck her out.
我现在谁都不想见
Yeah, I don't think I really wanna see anyone.
你还好吗
You okay?
没事 我应该打电话参加
Yeah. I think I'm gonna call in.
我想用打电话投票 我…
I think I'm gonna call in the vote. I think I'm gonna..
对 我不想...
Yeah. I don't wanna.
我想 兄弟...
Yeah, I think, man, it's
让大家知道 你在这里
let people kinda know you're here
展现一下力量
You know, show of force
你还好吗
Are you okay?
对 看起来比我想的更棒
Yeah. It looks better than I thought
棒太多了
Looks so much better.
对 没错 没错
Yeah, it does. It does
对 我觉得 大家会想知道
Yeah. I feel like people are gonna be like...
为什么不是我 知道吗
Why isn't it me? You know? Like..
当然 也可能是你 罗曼
Sure, I mean, it could've been you, Rome.
很可能会是你
It could easily have been you
这样只是为了好看
It's just... it's just marginal presentation shit
你拿到了超酷的社群媒体 对吧
You'll have something shit-hot. Socials. Right?
对 但这只是观感问题
Right. No... But it's just, you know, it's the optics
很蠢 但 缝针的地方...
It's dumb, but the stitches..
缝得很漂亮
They're good stitches. They're good
这有九成是表面工夫
This is 90% about the visuals
我是说 如果别人以为 我是因为没种 而退出
And I mean, just if, like, people think that I, like, pussied out
那我认为 我不该...你知道的
then I don't think that I should, you know..
怎么样  -对 我做不到 不行
Yeah.  -Yeah. I can't. No, I can't
因为 我看起来还可以
'Cause, you know, like, I look okay.
这看起来很好 所以...
Like, this looks fine, so, you know,
这很蠢 但是
it's fuckin' stupid, but.
为什么不是我?
Like, why isn't it me?
老弟
Bro.
好了
Okay. All right.
天啊 该死的
Oh, Jesus. Fuck.
你这个该死的混蛋
Oh, you fucking bastard
我爱你 兄弟  -混蛋 我恨你
I love you, man.  -Oh, shit. I fuckin' hate you
我们没事的 好吗
We'll be okay. All right?
该死的 裂开了  -我们会有一番作为的
Shit, it popped.  -We're gonna do good
合作 才能实现梦想
Teamwork makes the dreamwork
也可能是你
It could've been you
西蒙 你好吗
Simon, how are you?
很高兴见到你 谢谢你来
Good to see you. Thanks for being here
尤恩 来杯纽约最好的咖啡?
Ewan? New York's finest?
当然 谢谢
Absolutely. Appreciate it.
好 会议开始
All right, let's call this meeting to order.
所有董事全部出席
I note that all the directors are present
议程和资料都传下去了
The agenda and the information packs have been circulated
我就当大家都看过了
and I would like to take them as read.
GoJo董事会修改了他们的提议
We have a revised offer to consider from the GoJo board
他们为了让我们准备签字 下了很多功夫
and a lot of work has been done to get us to a position
就等董事会同意了
where we're ready to sign if the board agrees.
各位想必 也知道
As you also, of course, are aware
我们的联合CEO 也会提出其他策略上的选择
we will be hearing from our co-CEOs about strategic alternatives.
我们在之前的会议 已提过各种问题
We've aired the issues and heard from our advisors
也请顾问针对GoJo的提案 提出见解
on the GoJo proposal in the previous session.
现在 有请肯德尔
So, now, I like to hand the floor to Kendall
是的 GoJo的提议
Yeah. The... the GoJo offer.
一笔很不好的交易
Yeah, this deal... the deal is a bad deal.
GoJo的提议
The GoJo offer.
我跟罗曼 本来很骄傲 能促成这笔交易
We were proud to land it, me and Rome.
我们对它 了如指掌 但是 这笔交易不好
We know it inside-out, but it's a bad deal
如果各位执意要进行
And if you want it to go through
必须开除我 另请高明
you'll have to fire me and find someone else to take it through,
好吗
yeah?
我想...各位手上都有资料
I think you have your packs here
关于架构论点 和财务上的选项
with the structural arguments and the financing options and.
看 资料有厚厚一叠
Look, it's a nice thick pack.
我们击出了一支 漂亮的全垒打
We've knocked it out of the park,
GoJo马特森在垂死挣扎
and GoJo, Matsson, is flailing
这我们很清楚
We know that.
听我说
So, look, look.
我们是老交情了
We know each other.
我也跟你们都谈过
I've spoken to you all.
我喜欢 也尊敬各位
I like and respect every one of you
但 大家都不会改变主意了 对吧
But no one's gonna have their mind changed in here, right?
所以 我建议 直接投票
So, I suggest we move to the vote.
杀死...抱歉 GoJo的狗屁交易
Kill this, excuse me, GoJo bullshit
把他们的午餐 抢过来吃
and, you know, let's eat their lunch
肯
Ken.
怎么 要我为了走程序念一遍吗
What? You want me to read it out for due process?
别撑了 我们的票数够了
Come on. We have the votes
我想让西蒙来主持
I would rather Simon.
各位 就当是为我爸做的 好吗
Let's do it for my dad, guys. Yeah?
有没有人反对直接投票的?
Would anyone object to moving directly to a vote?
不反对
No.
好吧
Very well.
那...我赞成 我觉得 这是一笔很好的交易
So, yes. I think it's a good deal.
身为主席 我不能违背良心投反对票
I can't in good conscience as chair vote any other way
桑妮亚?  -赞成
Sonya?   -Yes.
黛安?  -赞成
Diane?   -Yes
肯德尔?  -你明知故问
Kendall?   -You know myvote.
我反对 我反对GoJo的交易
No. No to GoJo
赞成
Yes.
并且 我们想离开
And yes. We want out.
反对 我不赞成
No. I'm against.
最重要的是 不可伤人
First, do no harm.
反对
Nay.
我是肯德尔队的 宝贝
Team Ken, baby.
我反对
I'm a no.
罗曼?
Roman?
反对  -没错
Nope.  -That's fuckin' right
小西?
Shiv?
我有点…
Let's just.
我马上回来
just give me time.
小西?
Shiv?
没事 没事
It's all good, it's all good
失陪一下 我马上回来
Excuse me, I'll be right back
请稍等一下
Just a moment, please
保罗投票之后 现在票数是六比六
With Paul's vote, it's now six to six.
天啊  -六比六
Oh, my God.  -It's six to six.
我只是...  -嘿
I just...  -Hey.
你还好吧? 我们要赢了...
You okay? We have... we have it, we have it
是的…  -听我说...我们要赢了
Yeah...  -Look... we have it
好吗 我们要赢了
All right? We have it.
你是害怕了吗
Are... are you scared?
我不害怕..  -你不舒服吗
I'm not scared.  -Are you sick?
我才不害怕  -好 你还好吗
No, I'm not scared.  -Okay. Are you good?
我没事 可以让我静一下吗
Yeah. I just... Can I have a moment, please?
滚开 让我静一下
Just fuck off. I just... need a moment.
我要思考  -好
I wanna think.  -Okay
思考什么
Think about what?
思考 要把公司留下来
Whether you want us to keep the company
还是交给汤姆
or hand it over to Tom
和那个 害死我们爸爸的烂人?
and that piece of shit who killed our dad?
我可能改变主意了
I might have changed my mind
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
我对这家公司很好 对我们也很好
I'm good for this company. I'm... I'm good for us. We.
我们都投票的话 就能保有控制权
You know, we all vote, we keep control
否则 一切就永远毁了
We don't, then everything's over. Forever.
是这样的 我是为一台机器量身打造的齿轮
Here's the thing, I am like a cog built to fit only one machine.
如果你不让我做这个…
Like, if you don't let me do this..
这是我唯一会做的事
I mean, it's the one thing I know how to do
重点不只是你  -我知道
Well, it's not all about you.  -I know.
你不是最重要的人
Yeah, you are not the most important one.
我也 不这么觉得
I... I don't think I am.
少来...你明明就是这样想的
Yes, you do... You fucking do. You do
小西 最疯狂的事 莫过干 不让我...
Look, Shiv, honestly, it's so fucking crazy not to just let me..
我的意思是 这太蠢了
Now, I mean, it... it's stupid.
我们都有好处
We... we all get something here.
你改票 是对自己不利
I mean, you're voting against yourself.
你知道吗
You realize that?
小西 小西 拜托 你听我说
Shiv. Shiv, listen. Please
我求你 听我说
I beg you, listen.
我可以当CEO的
I can do this.
我觉得 你没办法做好
I don't think you'd be good at it.
什么? 我不敢相信…
What? I don't... I don't even believe you.
我不信  -真的
I don't believe you.  -I don't.
我认为 你没办法做好
I don't think that you would be good at this.
小西 真是够了
For fuck's sake, Shiv!
真是够了
I mean, for fuck's sake!
这是怎么回事
What the fuck is going on?
现在是六比六 小西可能跑票了
It... it's six to six, and we don't have Shiv's vote.
这完全说不... 逻辑 逻辑在哪里?
This doesn't make, like, logic. What's the logic?
我只是 不觉得你会做得很好
No, I just don't think you'd be good at it.
我觉得...如果我不能当CEO
I feel like... if I don't get to do this.
我觉得…
I... I feel like..
一切就完了
That's it.
觉得像是 我可能…
That's it. Like, I might, I might.
我可能会死掉
like I might die.
小西 我们可以回会议室吗 你可以投票吗
Shiv, can we go in that room? Can you just vote?
求求你
Please.
你不能当CEO
You can't be CEO
你不能 因为你杀了人
You can't because you killed someone.
你在...什么? 哪个?
What are... What? Which?
什么?  -等等 什么叫”哪个”
What?   -Wait, what do you mean, "which"?
什么? 你杀太多人 忘记是哪一个了吗?
What? Like, you killed so many people you forgot which one?
那不成问题
That's... that's not an issue
因为 根本没那回事
That didn't happen.
没有吗 什么意思
Wait, it didn't? As in what?
那只是 我随口说的
It's... it's just a thing I said.
那只是我随口说的 我编的
It's a thing I said. I made it up.
你编的?  -对 我...
You made it up?   -Yeah, I..
那段时期 我们都很不好过
I... it was a difficult time for us
我想我...无中生有了一件事
and I think I... you know, whatever mussed up something from nothing
希望 能在艰难时期 巩固手足之情
because I just... I wanted for us all to bond at a difficult moment
等等 那是你的计谋?
Wait, it was a move?
不...那时候有个小子
No, no, not... There was... there was a kid
所以 确实有个小子
So there was a kid
我喝了一杯酒 和一杯啤酒
I had, like, a toke and a beer and not..
我甚至没有上车
I... I didn't even get in the car, it's not.
等等 什么?  -你在说什么鬼?
Hold on. What?   -The fuck?
我心里很过意不去 我记错了
I felt bad and I... false-memoried it.
我已经戒酒了 我没问题的
Like, I'm totally clean. I can do this.
等等 那件事究竟有没有发生
Wait, did it happen or did it not happen?
没有
It did not happen.
没有发生 我人甚至不在那里
It did not happen. I wasn't even there.
没有发生
It did not happen.
老哥
Dude.
投我一票
Fucking vote for me.
拜托你 投我一票
Just please... vote for me.
小西 把票投给我
Shiv. Vote for me.
不要
No.
要  -不要
Yes.  -No.
小西 别这样  -不要
Shiv, don't do this.  -No.
你不能这样  -不要
You can't do this, Shiv.  -No.
要  -绝对不行
Yes.  -Absolutely not, man.
绝对不行  -不要
Absolutely not.  -No.
为什么  -你问我为什么?
Why?   -No. Why?
为什么  -我爱你 真的很爱你
Why? Just...  .  -I love you. I really..
我爱你 但我实在他妈受不了你
I love you, but I cannot fucking stomach you.
这太恶心了 实在有够恶心
This is fucking disgusting. It's disgusting
恶心?  -你好恶心
It's disgusting?   -You're disgusting!
没心没肝  -什么?
You're fucking heartless! -What?
这太疯狂了
It's fuckin' nuts!
完全没道理
It doesn't even make any sense!
我可是长子  -天啊
I'm the eldest boy! -God!
我是长子  -才不是
I am the eldest boy! -You're not.
爸很重视传承
And, you know, it... this... it mattered to him.
他希望公司能持续下去
He wanted this to go on.
是啦 但她才是血脉
Well, I mean, she's the bloodline, though
什么? 我们都是爸的血脉
What? I'm the... I'm the bloodline. We're all the fucking bloodline
我是说 如果你想打这张牌
No, I just mean if you're gonna play that card
爸一直觉得 你的不是真的
Dad's view was yours weren't real.
你他妈说什么  -就是 你的血脉 不是真的
What the fuck did you just say?   -Well, just not real-real.
罗曼...  -爸是这么说的
Rome...  -Well, that's just what Dad said
我只是重复了他的话
I'm just saying what Dad said
别说了 你这个贱胚
Well, don't say it. You fucking cuck.
他们俩不知道是哪里来的
They are a pair of randos.
一个是买来的
One is a buy-in
另一个是 拉瓦和资料室的某人生的 对吧
the other is half Rava half some filing cabinet guy, right?
你...
You...
搞什么
What the fuck?
放开他  -你他妈刚刚说什么?
Let go of him! -What the fuck did you say?
你在做什么
What the fuck are you doing?
住手  -你他妈说什么
Stop! -What the fuck did you say?
老天爷啊  -你没有小孩
Fuck's sake.  -You have no kids
小西 别这样 别这样,  -等等 等一下
Shiv, don't! Don't do this! -Okay, hold on. Hold on a second
放开我  -她怀孕了
Get the fuck off me! -She's fucking pregnant
混蛋  -放开我
you piece of shit.  -Get off me!
我的天啊
Jesus Christ!
开什么玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?
小西 不可以 等一下
Shiv, no! Wait!
小西 等等
Shiv,  Wait!
去死吧你
Fuck you.
放过她 行不行
Can you just fucking leave her?
幼稚鬼
Fucking child.
我们去找弗兰克
Let's hit... let's hit Frank.
我们说服他
Let's offer Frank
还是有希望的
We can still... we can still do this
狗屁 成不了事的 算了
Bullshit, man. Come on. It's fucking nothing. Stop
不对 一定有办法
No, there... there's something here.
一定有切入点
There's an angle.
不 没戏唱了
No, no, it's fuck-all, man.
那全是胶水 和没人看的节目
It's bits of glue and broken shows
是假新闻 天杀的...
fuckin' phony news, fucking..
别硬撑了
Come on.
我们可以的 还是可以赢
We have this. We can still do this, man
我的天啊 现在什么都不是了 好吗 什么都不是了
Oh, my God, man, it's nothing. Okay? It's just nothing.
什么都不是 不要再执迷不悟
It's fucking nothing. Stop it
不对...
No..
就是
Yeah.
嘿 我们都是假货
Hey. We are bullshit
我们不是假货
We are not bullshit.
你是假货 你是天杀的假货
You are bullshit. You're fucking bullshit, man.
我是假货 她也是假货
I'm fucking bullshit. She's bullshit
一切都虚的
It's all fucking nothing
我这么跟你说 是因为我知道 好吗
And I'm telling you this because I... I know it, okay?
我们什么都不是
We're nothing
好了
Okay.
嘿 不好意思
Hey, so, pardon me.
进行到哪里了
Where are we?
肯  -我在想 也许我们应该...
Ken.  -I was thinking maybe we... that we should maybe
先休会 等到...
adjourn the meeting and re..
肯 肯 结束了
Ken, Ken, it's done
七票对六票
Seven, six.
我们卖给GoJo了
We sell to GoJo.
你的票数不够
You don't have it.
我们赢了
We're good.
很好
Okay.
所以 现在是怎样 拿钱走人?
So, what are you thinkin'? Golden parachute?
或是再干一场
Or one last rodeo.
少来了
Go on.
你有什么想法
What do you think?
我在想 当年应该趁他在摇蓝里 就宰了他
I'm thinkin' they should have slit his throat in the cradle.
那个自然不在话下
Well, I mean, goes without saying
真为你高兴
I'm thrilled for you.
谢谢  -咱们好好干一场
I appreciate you.  -Let's fuckin' do it
找时间聊吧  -嘿 兄弟
Please, let's talk.  -Hey, man
漂亮的逆转
Great one.
输家永远不会得胜
The losers never triumph.
我一直希望你能出头
I was always hoping, you know?
咱们聊聊 我罩你
So, let's chat. I got you.
卡洛丽娜呢?
Where's Karolina?
卡洛丽娜?
Karolina?
她…
She's...
汤姆 恭喜  -嘿 兄弟
Congratulations, Tom.  -Hey, buddy
嘿 嘿 谢谢
Hey, hey. Thank you
我只想说声恭喜
I just... I just wanted to say congrats
谢了
Thanks.
对 那…
And yeah. So..
嘿 汤姆  -嘿
Hey, Tom.  -Hey.
真是太棒了  -新气象 对吧
Just phenomenal.  -The pastor's new. Right?
没错  -新的时代来了
Yes, it is.  -This is it
谢谢
Thank you.
情况如何
Yes, how's it all lookin'?
有计划吗 开始计划了吗  -我想跟格丽谈
Plans? Planning?   -Yeah, I wanna talk to Gerri
格丽会懂的 她不怕黑
Yeah. Gerri gets it. She's not afraid of the dark
还有谁
And who else?
弗兰克死定了 卡尔也是
Frank, dead. Karl, dead
我可不需要他们两个监视我
I really don't need those two old cunts on my shoulder
至于你
You?
你搞砸了 四人组的小弟
You fucked it, man. Quad man.
马特森讨厌你 他要清理门户
Matsson hates you. Wants to clean up
可恶
Fuck
你是个彻头彻尾的烂人
You are a fuckin' piece of shit.
但 我会罩你
But I got you.
我正好有足够的筹码
I got just enough capital
我会罩你
I got you.
好的 好了 嘿  大家好
Okay. All right. Hey. Guys
嗨 好  -可以了吗
Hi. Fine.  -Good. So, we're good to go?
沟通似乎出了点问题
Seems to be a little bit of a communication breakdown.
我不介意签字
I don't mind signing the fucking thing
不用说服我
I don't need to be talked into that.
我们需要你现在进来
We need you to come in right now
完成仪式  -我只是...
to complete this ceremony.  -I just need.
把纸拿来让我签
Bring me the piece of paper and I'll sign it.
我们要签就在桌上签
If we're gonna do this, we're gonna do it at the desk
我要跟他同时在那里签字吗?
I have to be in the room with him and sign the thing?
这是CEO要做的事
This is being a CEO
拍张照就可以收工了  -还要拍照
One quick photo, you're done.  -And it's a photo-op
我说过我不拍照
I already told you, I'm not taking a fucking photo
好 来吧 不用 来吧
Let's take...  Okay, let's do it. No, no, let's fucking do it.
拍吧 想咋拍就咋拍
Take a photo, take all the fuckin' pictures you want.
早死早超生 大日子
See where you lead me. Big day
真开心 好东西  -太好了
Happy, happy, good stuff.  -Okay.
太好了  -你好吗
Great.  -How are ya?
好 那就开始吧 谢谢  -好的
Okay, here we go. Inking...  Okay
动作快
Quick, quick
这个可以办退货吗
What's the return policy on this, by the way?
恭喜  -谢谢 谢谢
Congratulations.  -Thank you, thank you
爱你 罗曼  -谢谢 兄弟
Love you, Roman.  -Thank you, man
把弗兰克和卡尔叫进来
Okay, let's get Frank and Karl in here.
拍大合照  GoJo团队 弗兰克和卡尔
Group photo, GoJo team, Frank and Karl, okay?
大家站近一点 麻烦了
Guys, get closer together, please
站近一点 笑一个
Closer together. Good. Smile
太好了 一二三
Wonderful. One, two, three.
这就是新团队 好的
This is the new team. All right.
耶稣和他的门徒
Jesus and his disciples.
连犹大都在
Even... even Judas is in the room.
说得好  -说得好
Oh, there we go.  -There we go.
好了 要拍一张GoJo团队的吗
Okay. Want just a GoJo one?
好 这张只拍GoJo的人
Yeah, let's do a GoJo. GoJo photo.
就只有你们三个  -好的
Okay, just the three of you.  -All right
好的  -三剑客
Okay.  -Three Musketeers
预备 一二三
There you go. One, two, three.
太好了  -来拍独照
Wonderful.  -Let's just do a single.
马特森自己拍一张 好的
Single on Matsson. Okay
嘿 我20分钟后 会上车 你可以一起来
Hey, I got a car in 20 if you wanna join.
好 谢谢 谢谢
All right, thankyou, thankyou
派对开始
Let's party!
开香槟  -狂欢吧
Little bubbly-bubbly! -Let's party
香槟怎么还没拿出来
Why isn't there champagne already out?
恭喜
Congratulations
别客气
Oh, no.
全剧终